[{"filename": "1.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45696060", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "10.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45586255", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "100.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45104906", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1000.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 318, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44104833", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 224, "name": "SolveCase", "long_name": "SolveCase( ulong CaseNo)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["CaseNo"], "filename": "1000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 73, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1001.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44095852", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1001.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1002.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44095742", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1002.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1003.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44095241", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 128, "name": "dp", "long_name": "dp( int ini , int fin)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["ini", "fin"], "filename": "1003.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1003.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1004.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 326, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44094016", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 13, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 231, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1004.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1005.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44089322", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 96, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( vector<int> a , int l , int r)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "l", "r"], "filename": "1005.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1005.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1006.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44083727", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1006.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1007.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44074395", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 48, "name": "cnt", "long_name": "cnt( ll i , ll j)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1007.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 46, "name": "flips", "long_name": "flips( ll i , ll j)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1007.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "configure", "long_name": "configure( ll i , ll j)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1007.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1007.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1008.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44074201", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 48, "name": "cnt", "long_name": "cnt( ll i , ll j)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 46, "name": "flips", "long_name": "flips( ll i , ll j)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "configure", "long_name": "configure( ll i , ll j)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1009.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44070461", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1009.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "101.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45103573", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1010.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44058310", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1011.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44056239", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 10, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 60, "parameters": [], "filename": "1011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1012.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44056230", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 10, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1012.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1013.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44051236", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 217, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1013.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1014.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 387, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44050838", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 124, "parameters": [], "filename": "1014.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1015.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44049104", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1015.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1016.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 463, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44030336", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 456, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1016.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1017.cpp", "nloc": 102, "token_count": 565, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44018279", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 35, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "BigMod", "long_name": "BigMod( LL B , LL P , LL M)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["B", "P", "M"], "filename": "1017.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 27, "name": "maxDivide", "long_name": "maxDivide( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 179, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1017.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 45, "name": "isUgly", "long_name": "isUgly( LL no)", "start_line": 181, "end_line": 193, "parameters": ["no"], "filename": "1017.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 78, "name": "myXOR", "long_name": "myXOR( LL x , LL y)", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 221, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1017.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 259, "end_line": 325, "parameters": [], "filename": "1017.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1018.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44005641", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "1018.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1019.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44005548", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1019.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "102.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 307, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45102638", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 300, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "102.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1020.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 293, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/44004752", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 32, "name": "count0", "long_name": "count0( int l , int r)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 32, "name": "count1", "long_name": "count1( int l , int r)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1021.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43985929", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "1021.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1022.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43951766", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 122, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 54, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1023.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43946801", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 125, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( vector<int> & a , int n)", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["a", "n"], "filename": "1023.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 81, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "1023.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1024.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 145, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43946693", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1024.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1025.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 84, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43946229", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 61, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "1025.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1026.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43935921", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1026.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1027.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43927439", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1027.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1028.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43927433", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1028.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1029.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43913279", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "103.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45101564", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1030.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43909346", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1030.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1031.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43907792", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1031.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1032.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43903636", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1032.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1033.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 275, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43891176", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1033.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1034.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43886843", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1034.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1035.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43881492", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 70, "parameters": [], "filename": "1035.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1036.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43878127", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1037.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43826203", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1037.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1038.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 403, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43822679", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 75, "token_count": 396, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "1038.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 151, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1039.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43805215", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "104.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45100948", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1040.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43801849", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1040.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1041.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43790853", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ull a , ull b)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1041.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1041.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1042.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43790802", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1042.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1042.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1043.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43781186", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 171, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int i , int j)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1043.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 56, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1043.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1044.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43763356", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 283, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1044.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 52, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1045.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43744465", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1045.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1046.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43741637", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1046.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1047.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43739542", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1047.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1048.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43739513", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1048.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1049.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43726661", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1049.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "105.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45097725", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1050.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 268, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43726469", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 19, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 26, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "debug", "long_name": "debug( int n , ...)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["n", "..."], "filename": "1050.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 62, "name": "lcs", "long_name": "lcs()", "start_line": 203, "end_line": 219, "parameters": [], "filename": "1050.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 88, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 223, "end_line": 257, "parameters": [], "filename": "1050.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1051.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43724424", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1052.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43722045", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 264, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "1052.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 149, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1053.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 277, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43721398", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 31, "name": "filldata", "long_name": "filldata()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1053.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 47, "name": "get_answert", "long_name": "get_answert()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1053.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1053.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1055.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43713630", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "23500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1055.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1056.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43710192", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1057.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 338, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43707653", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 57, "token_count": 331, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1057.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 127, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1058.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43697293", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "calc", "long_name": "calc( int l , int r)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1059.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43697170", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 23, "name": "calc", "long_name": "calc( int l , int r)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "106.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 479, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45083934", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 287, "name": "merge", "long_name": "merge( int arr [ ] , int left , int right)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["]", "left", "right"], "filename": "106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1060.cpp", "nloc": 76, "token_count": 365, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43691773", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 30, "used_headers": 29, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 288, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 187, "parameters": [], "filename": "1060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1061.cpp", "nloc": 2, "token_count": 89, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43690330", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 71, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 3, "parameters": [], "filename": "1061.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1062.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43684937", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1063.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43681425", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1063.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1064.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43666353", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1064.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1065.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43664494", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1065.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1066.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 254, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43654797", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 243, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1066.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1067.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43653372", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1067.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1068.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 274, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43649339", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1068.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1069.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 80, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43645323", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 60, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "107.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 478, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45083918", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 286, "name": "merge", "long_name": "merge( int arr [ ] , int left , int right)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["]", "left", "right"], "filename": "107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1070.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43641499", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 234, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "1070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1071.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43641445", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 260, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1072.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43641330", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 20, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll n , ll pos)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["n", "pos"], "filename": "1072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "Set", "long_name": "Set( ll n , ll pos)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["n", "pos"], "filename": "1072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 260, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 223, "parameters": [], "filename": "1072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1073.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43641279", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 20, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll n , ll pos)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["n", "pos"], "filename": "1073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "Set", "long_name": "Set( ll n , ll pos)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["n", "pos"], "filename": "1073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 260, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 223, "parameters": [], "filename": "1073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1074.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 326, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43641231", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 20, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll n , ll pos)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["n", "pos"], "filename": "1074.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "Set", "long_name": "Set( ll n , ll pos)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["n", "pos"], "filename": "1074.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 257, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 223, "parameters": [], "filename": "1074.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1075.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43640034", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "1075.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1076.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43639495", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1076.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1077.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43638755", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1078.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43634637", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1078.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1079.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43633042", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 93, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1079.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "108.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45083838", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1080.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 270, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43632112", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "4600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1080.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1081.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 395, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43624346", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 288, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1081.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 81, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "1081.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1082.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 298, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43623387", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 191, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1082.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 81, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 141, "parameters": [], "filename": "1082.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1083.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43622983", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 143, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1083.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 81, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1083.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1084.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43622912", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1084.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1085.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43621166", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 2, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1085.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1086.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 119, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43617570", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1087.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 119, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43617539", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1087.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1088.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43616131", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1088.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1089.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 300, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43615801", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 293, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1089.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 95, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "109.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45078735", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 37, "name": "diff", "long_name": "diff( int x , int y)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 219, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1090.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43613952", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1090.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1091.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 660, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43608589", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 99, "name": "seg::init", "long_name": "seg::init( int i , int l , int r)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["i", "l", "r"], "filename": "1091.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 117, "name": "seg::update", "long_name": "seg::update( int i , int l , int r , int pos , int val)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["i", "l", "r", "pos", "val"], "filename": "1091.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 107, "name": "seg::get", "long_name": "seg::get( int i , int l , int r , int a , int b)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["i", "l", "r", "a", "b"], "filename": "1091.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 286, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1091.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1092.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 267, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43606135", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1092.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1093.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43585788", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1093.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1094.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43580083", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 344, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1095.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43576746", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 106, "name": "cl", "long_name": "cl( int l , int r)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1096.cpp", "nloc": 85, "token_count": 604, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43576711", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 291, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "modInv", "long_name": "modInv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 66, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "1096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 68, "end_line": 78, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "1096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "mpower", "long_name": "mpower( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 80, "end_line": 92, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "1096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 51, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 94, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1097.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43575050", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "1097.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1098.cpp", "nloc": 83, "token_count": 613, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43575053", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 9, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 45, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "abs", "long_name": "abs( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 41, "name": "isOut", "long_name": "isOut( ll y , ll x , ll y1 , ll x1)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 42, "parameters": ["y", "x", "y1", "x1"], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "edge::edge", "long_name": "edge::edge( ll x)", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 24, "name": "edge::operator <", "long_name": "edge::operator <( const edge & l) const", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["l"], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "desc", "long_name": "desc( edge a , edge b)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 259, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 68, "end_line": 106, "parameters": [], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1099.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43575039", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1099.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "11.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45585894", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "11.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "110.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45078661", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 214, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1100.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 95, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43565071", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1101.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 116, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43561997", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1102.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43559059", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "15700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1102.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1103.cpp", "nloc": 100, "token_count": 553, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43547123", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 85, "name": "isPrime", "long_name": "isPrime( ll n)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 77, "name": "seive", "long_name": "seive()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 263, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 251, "parameters": [], "filename": "1103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 255, "end_line": 299, "parameters": [], "filename": "1103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1104.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 879, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43545369", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "tick", "long_name": "tick()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( T a , T b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( T a , T b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( T a , T b , T c)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "mod_neg", "long_name": "mod_neg( T a , T b)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 73, "name": "mulmod", "long_name": "mulmod( LL a , LL b , LL m)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 51, "name": "expo", "long_name": "expo( T e , T n)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["e", "n"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 66, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( T e , T n , T m)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["e", "n", "m"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 97, "name": "extended_euclid", "long_name": "extended_euclid( T a , T b , T & x , T & y)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 46, "name": "mod_inverse", "long_name": "mod_inverse( T a , T n)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["a", "n"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 251, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 191, "parameters": [], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 117, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1105.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43523691", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1106.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43521841", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1107.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43516248", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1108.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43514891", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1109.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43513941", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "111.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 270, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45078631", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 37, "name": "diff", "long_name": "diff( int x , int y)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1110.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43510248", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1111.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43487642", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1112.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43481178", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1113.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 361, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43479668", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "_f", "long_name": "_f( const char * name , T && arg)", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 20, "parameters": ["name", "arg"], "filename": "1113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 60, "name": "_f", "long_name": "_f( const char * names , T && arg , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["names", "arg", "args"], "filename": "1113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char ** argv)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 80, "parameters": ["argc", "argv"], "filename": "1113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 42, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1114.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43474331", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1115.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 267, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43469365", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 96, "name": "maxim", "long_name": "maxim( int * p , int n , int o , int l)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["p", "n", "o", "l"], "filename": "1115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1116.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43467646", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1117.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 370, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43465535", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 72, "name": "fpow", "long_name": "fpow( ll n , ll k , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["n", "k", "mod"], "filename": "1117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 85, "name": "isPrime", "long_name": "isPrime( ll n)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1118.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43463102", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 55, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1119.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43457764", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 244, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1119.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "112.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45078177", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 37, "name": "diff", "long_name": "diff( int x , int y)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1120.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43444706", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 132, "name": "answer", "long_name": "answer( int n , vector<int> A)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["n", "A"], "filename": "1120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1121.cpp", "nloc": 95, "token_count": 641, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43441913", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 36, "name": "Less::operator ( )", "long_name": "Less::operator ( )( const pair<int,int> & x , const pair<int,int> & y) const", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 36, "name": "More::operator ( )", "long_name": "More::operator ( )( const pair<int,int> & x , const pair<int,int> & y) const", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 41, "name": "bit_query", "long_name": "bit_query( int i)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 41, "name": "bit_set", "long_name": "bit_set( int x , int v)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["x", "v"], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 53, "name": "pow_mod", "long_name": "pow_mod( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 42, "name": "GCD", "long_name": "GCD( int a , int b)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 282, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 213, "parameters": [], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1122.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 281, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43437336", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 61, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 20, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 199, "name": "kadane", "long_name": "kadane( vector<int> & num)", "start_line": 22, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 42, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1123.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43435248", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1124.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43433054", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1125.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 298, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43422272", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 30, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 263, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 104, "parameters": [], "filename": "1125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1126.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 757, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43420391", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 16, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 7, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 23, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "llin", "long_name": "llin()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "ldin", "long_name": "ldin()", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "chin", "long_name": "chin()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "strin", "long_name": "strin()", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "No", "long_name": "No()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "NO", "long_name": "NO()", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "Yes", "long_name": "Yes()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "YES", "long_name": "YES()", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 69, "name": "fmin_i", "long_name": "fmin_i( vlli v)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 69, "name": "fmax_i", "long_name": "fmax_i( vlli v)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 42, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 62, "name": "lmin_i", "long_name": "lmin_i( vlli v)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 62, "name": "lmax_i", "long_name": "lmax_i( vlli v)", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 44, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 46, "name": "min_e", "long_name": "min_e( vlli v)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 46, "name": "max_e", "long_name": "max_e( vlli v)", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 114, "name": "make_prime", "long_name": "make_prime( vb & v)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1127.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 261, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43417382", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 254, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1128.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43411694", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1129.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43401962", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1129.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "113.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45077065", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 240, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1130.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43398559", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1131.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43398222", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1132.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43395277", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "1132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 62, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1133.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43395247", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "1133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 20, "name": "rnd", "long_name": "rnd( ll x)", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 70, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1134.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43393602", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1134.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1135.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 308, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43388829", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1136.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 284, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43388784", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1137.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 236, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43388626", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1138.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43388609", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 209, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1139.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43379562", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "1139.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "114.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45076699", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1140.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 258, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43379448", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 50, "parameters": [], "filename": "1140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1141.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 260, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43355698", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "69800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1142.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43345202", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 249, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1143.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43293948", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "1143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1144.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 302, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43287909", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 263, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "1144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1145.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43282800", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 52, "parameters": [], "filename": "1145.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1146.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43269354", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1146.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1147.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 112, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43267137", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1147.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1148.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43265242", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1149.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43264520", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "115.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45074503", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1150.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 574, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43235423", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "fpow", "long_name": "fpow( ll n , ll k , ll p = MOD)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["n", "k", "MOD"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll a , ll p = MOD)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["a", "MOD"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 91, "name": "Sqrt", "long_name": "Sqrt( ll x)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 69, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 83, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( ll & no)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["no"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1151.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 100, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43173977", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 93, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1151.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1152.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43172155", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1153.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 121, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43159671", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1154.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43133317", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 21, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1154.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1155.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43117755", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1155.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1156.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 362, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43116269", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 355, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1156.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1157.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43103803", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1158.cpp", "nloc": 8, "token_count": 85, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43098290", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 17, "parameters": [], "filename": "1158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1159.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 109, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43084819", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "116.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45073649", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1160.cpp", "nloc": 68, "token_count": 579, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43081209", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 52, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 74, "end_line": 74, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 65, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 76, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 78, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 92, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 94, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "modinv", "long_name": "modinv( ll a , ll p)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 110, "parameters": ["a", "p"], "filename": "1160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1161.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43079462", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1161.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1162.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43076805", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1162.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1163.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43076561", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1163.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1164.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43055272", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1164.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1165.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43044596", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 68, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( int sz)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["sz"], "filename": "1165.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1165.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1166.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43034990", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1167.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43034414", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1167.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1168.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 87, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43028344", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 68, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1169.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43027176", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "117.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 458, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45073531", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 36, "name": "UndirectedGraph::AddEdge", "long_name": "UndirectedGraph::AddEdge( int x , int val , bool t)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["x", "val", "t"], "filename": "117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 121, "name": "UndirectedGraph::MatchNode", "long_name": "UndirectedGraph::MatchNode( int Node)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["Node"], "filename": "117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 116, "name": "UndirectedGraph::Coverage", "long_name": "UndirectedGraph::Coverage()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 83, "name": "Citire", "long_name": "Citire()", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 14, "name": "Rezolvare", "long_name": "Rezolvare()", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 141, "parameters": [], "filename": "117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 16, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1170.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43009448", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1171.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 122, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/43001858", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1172.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42991606", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1173.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42960567", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 55, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1173.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1174.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42957852", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1174.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1175.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42957304", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 204, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1175.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 33, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1175.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1176.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 284, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42951910", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 105, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1176.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1176.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1177.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 332, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42947393", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 209, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( int idx , int status)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["idx", "status"], "filename": "1177.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1177.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1178.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42913952", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1178.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1179.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 92, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42910532", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 85, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "118.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45071492", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1180.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42907890", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "1180.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1181.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42902832", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "1181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1182.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42901876", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1182.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1183.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 362, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42897370", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 23, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int a , int b)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 323, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 68, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1184.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42894977", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 240, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1184.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1185.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42894364", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 11, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1185.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1186.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42886242", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 203, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1186.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1187.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42885904", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1187.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1188.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42885331", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "adelkhah", "long_name": "adelkhah()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1188.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1189.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42884916", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 283, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1189.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 113, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "119.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45070998", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "119.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1190.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42884815", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 283, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1191.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 93, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42875073", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 70, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1192.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42867501", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1193.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42855793", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1195.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42846595", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 125, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int i , int j , int counter)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["i", "j", "counter"], "filename": "1195.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1195.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1196.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42841320", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "1196.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1197.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42836262", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1198.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42835241", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1198.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1199.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 312, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42833253", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1199.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "12.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45585698", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 234, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "12.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "120.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45070300", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1200.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42832348", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1201.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 344, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42808837", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 241, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1202.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42798101", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1203.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42794281", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1204.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42773595", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1205.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 284, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42773479", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 271, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1205.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1206.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 286, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42773424", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 273, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1207.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 255, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42772545", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 51, "token_count": 247, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 52, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1208.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42761779", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1209.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42748879", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "1209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "121.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45070031", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1210.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42745204", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "printprecise", "long_name": "printprecise( double l , ll precision)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["l", "precision"], "filename": "1210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1211.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 93, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42743556", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 70, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 14, "parameters": [], "filename": "1211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1212.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42734485", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 37, "name": "pilot", "long_name": "pilot()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1213.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42733879", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 37, "name": "pilot", "long_name": "pilot()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1214.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42725060", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 0, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1215.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42724589", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1216.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42722686", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1217.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42708036", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1217.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1218.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42707395", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1218.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1219.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42705884", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1219.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "122.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45069983", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 288, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1220.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42703150", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1220.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1221.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42701159", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1222.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 102, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42699764", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 95, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1223.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42693968", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1225.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42678802", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1226.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42671157", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "1226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "1226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 59, "name": "modPow", "long_name": "modPow( ll x , ll n)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x", "n"], "filename": "1226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1227.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 265, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42665619", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "78300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 241, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1227.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1228.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42662950", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 316, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1228.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1229.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42656088", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 278, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1229.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "123.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45069956", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 292, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1230.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42607130", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 223, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1230.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1231.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42566615", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 69, "name": "flip", "long_name": "flip( int i , int j)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1231.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1231.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1232.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42556968", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "1232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1233.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42555477", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1233.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1234.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42555048", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1235.cpp", "nloc": 94, "token_count": 483, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42547543", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 23, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 23, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 27, "name": "diff", "long_name": "diff( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 21, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( ll a)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 117, "name": "pairsort", "long_name": "pairsort( int a [ ] , int b [ ] , int n)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["]", "]", "n"], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 230, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 197, "parameters": [], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1236.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42542943", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1237.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 97, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42540329", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 74, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 16, "parameters": [], "filename": "1237.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1238.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 478, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42531589", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 51, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( const string & s , char c)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "1238.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "1238.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 61, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "1238.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 141, "parameters": [], "filename": "1238.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1239.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42527781", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "124.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45068503", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1240.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42527755", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1240.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1241.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 99, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42493176", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1241.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1242.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42492002", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1242.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1243.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42491664", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1243.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1244.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 313, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42490967", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 306, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 60, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1245.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 313, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42490955", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 306, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1245.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 119, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1246.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42489467", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1246.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1247.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42484479", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1247.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1248.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 277, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42469738", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 270, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1248.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1249.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42467688", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "125.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45068454", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1250.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42454642", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "1250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1251.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42454636", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1251.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1252.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42450892", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1253.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42444959", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1253.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1254.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42441264", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "LSB", "long_name": "LSB( int i)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "1254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1255.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42441163", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 77, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1256.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42438796", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 243, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 40, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1257.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42438427", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1258.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 412, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42431615", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 23, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int a , int b)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 365, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "1258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1259.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42431518", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1259.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "126.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45068167", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1260.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42412138", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1260.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1261.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 100, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42378356", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 93, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1261.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1262.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42363580", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1263.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42359255", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1263.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1264.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42353533", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "1264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1265.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42353461", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1265.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1266.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42351616", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1267.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42351202", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1268.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42351160", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1269.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42350483", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1269.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "127.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 305, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45067770", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 273, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1270.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42341578", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 283, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1271.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42339259", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 52, "name": "find_mx_sum", "long_name": "find_mx_sum()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1272.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42337625", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1272.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1273.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42336248", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1273.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1274.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 588, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42304956", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "strtoll", "long_name": "strtoll( string s)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lltostr", "long_name": "lltostr( ll n)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 83, "name": "fastscan", "long_name": "fastscan( ll & number)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["number"], "filename": "1274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 77, "name": "sieve", "long_name": "sieve()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 76, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "modInverse", "long_name": "modInverse( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "1274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 217, "parameters": [], "filename": "1274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1275.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42297035", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1275.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1276.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42296801", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 147, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int i , int j)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1277.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 482, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42290493", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 32, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 23, "name": "sol", "long_name": "sol( int i)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "1277.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 239, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 185, "parameters": [], "filename": "1277.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1278.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42286685", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1279.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42284044", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 320, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1279.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "128.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45067749", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1280.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42277934", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 68, "parameters": [], "filename": "1280.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1281.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 318, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42276515", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1281.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "boost", "long_name": "boost()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1281.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1281.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1282.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42274614", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1282.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1283.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42273898", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 133, "name": "solution", "long_name": "solution()", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "1283.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 14, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "1283.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1284.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42263404", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1285.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42259664", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1285.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1286.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42259579", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 274, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1286.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1287.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42256612", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 132, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int i , int j)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1287.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 48, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1287.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1288.cpp", "nloc": 146, "token_count": 1089, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42250039", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 18, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 84, "name": "CountDistinct", "long_name": "CountDistinct( vector<T> a)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "Sort", "long_name": "Sort( vector<T> a)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 50, "name": "Prime", "long_name": "Prime( T n)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 90, "name": "GetDistinctSet", "long_name": "GetDistinctSet( vector<T> a)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 96, "name": "GetDistinctMap", "long_name": "GetDistinctMap( vector<T> a)", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 44, "name": "Gcd", "long_name": "Gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 29, "name": "ToLower", "long_name": "ToLower( char ch)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["ch"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 29, "name": "ToUpper", "long_name": "ToUpper( char ch)", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["ch"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 43, "name": "ToLower", "long_name": "ToLower( string s)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 43, "name": "ToUpper", "long_name": "ToUpper( string s)", "start_line": 177, "end_line": 187, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 48, "name": "ChangeRegister", "long_name": "ChangeRegister( char ch)", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 199, "parameters": ["ch"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 43, "name": "ChangeRegister", "long_name": "ChangeRegister( string s)", "start_line": 203, "end_line": 213, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 46, "name": "StringToVector", "long_name": "StringToVector( string s)", "start_line": 217, "end_line": 229, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "YesNo", "long_name": "YesNo( bool ok)", "start_line": 233, "end_line": 239, "parameters": ["ok"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "YESNO", "long_name": "YESNO( bool ok)", "start_line": 243, "end_line": 249, "parameters": ["ok"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 47, "name": "ReverseString", "long_name": "ReverseString( string s)", "start_line": 253, "end_line": 265, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 65, "name": "GetDigits", "long_name": "GetDigits( int number)", "start_line": 269, "end_line": 287, "parameters": ["number"], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 291, "end_line": 331, "parameters": [], "filename": "1288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1289.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42246006", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1289.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "129.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45067534", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "129.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1290.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42240606", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1290.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1291.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42237403", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 68, "name": "input", "long_name": "input()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1291.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 73, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1291.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 35, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1291.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1292.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42236141", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1292.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1293.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42231638", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1293.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1294.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42222806", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "5500 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1294.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1295.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42214650", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1296.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42202889", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1296.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1297.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42189871", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1298.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42156330", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 239, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1298.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1299.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42129296", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1299.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "13.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 386, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45582818", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 142, "name": "qsort", "long_name": "qsort( int l , int r , int x)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["l", "r", "x"], "filename": "13.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 89, "name": "work", "long_name": "work()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "13.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "13.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "130.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45067079", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1300.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42117870", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1301.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42114150", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1301.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1302.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42106337", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1302.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1303.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42102564", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 93, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1303.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1304.cpp", "nloc": 72, "token_count": 595, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42101112", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 42, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "debug", "long_name": "debug( vector<T> vec)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["vec"], "filename": "1304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 73, "name": "debug", "long_name": "debug( vector<vector<T>> vec)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["vec"], "filename": "1304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 217, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 108, "parameters": [], "filename": "1304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 43, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 110, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1305.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 103, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42090105", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1305.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1306.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 313, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42087365", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 298, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1307.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42070786", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 97, "name": "compute", "long_name": "compute( int i , int j)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1307.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1307.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1308.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42070758", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 70, "name": "compute", "long_name": "compute( int i , int j)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1309.cpp", "nloc": 71, "token_count": 433, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42065300", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 146, "name": "convert_array", "long_name": "convert_array( int * road , int * road2 , int oldArray_siz , int * newArray_siz)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["road", "road2", "oldArray_siz", "newArray_siz"], "filename": "1309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 98, "name": "cum_sum_by_negative", "long_name": "cum_sum_by_negative( int * arr , int siz)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["arr", "siz"], "filename": "1309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 209, "parameters": [], "filename": "1309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "131.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45063002", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 20, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1310.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42031584", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1311.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42024454", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1311.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1312.cpp", "nloc": 9, "token_count": 81, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42023880", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 59, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "1312.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1313.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42020436", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1313.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1314.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 304, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42018702", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 110, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1314.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1314.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1315.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 324, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42017740", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 110, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1315.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1315.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1316.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42009070", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1317.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/42003272", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1317.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1318.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41998128", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1318.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1319.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41997916", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "132.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 318, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45059402", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 91, "name": "aug", "long_name": "aug( int ini)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 20, "parameters": ["ini"], "filename": "132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 22, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1320.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 238, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41997296", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1321.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41997266", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1321.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1322.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 509, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41990466", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 86, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 103, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read( mitsuha & x)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "chtholly::write", "long_name": "chtholly::write( mitsuha x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "chtholly::fuhao", "long_name": "chtholly::fuhao()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1323.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41985936", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 13, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1323.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1325.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41985607", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1325.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1326.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 264, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41973970", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 257, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1326.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1327.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41968628", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1327.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1328.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41964567", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1328.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 33, "name": "copy", "long_name": "copy( ll n)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1328.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1329.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41954759", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1329.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "133.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45056384", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1330.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41953796", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "1330.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1331.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 322, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41953554", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 30, "name": "q1", "long_name": "q1( int i , int j)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1331.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 30, "name": "q2", "long_name": "q2( int i , int j)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1331.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 236, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1331.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1332.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41952987", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1333.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41947839", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1334.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 280, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41936095", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 241, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1334.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1335.cpp", "nloc": 103, "token_count": 599, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41932519", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 13, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 32, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 13, "name": "two", "long_name": "two( int n)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 20, "name": "test", "long_name": "test( int n , int b)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "set_bit", "long_name": "set_bit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "unset_bit", "long_name": "unset_bit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "last_bit", "long_name": "last_bit( int n)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 31, "name": "ones", "long_name": "ones( int n)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 163, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 67, "name": "modPow", "long_name": "modPow( ll a , ll b , ll MOD)", "start_line": 177, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "modInverse", "long_name": "modInverse( ll a , ll p)", "start_line": 207, "end_line": 213, "parameters": ["a", "p"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 41, "name": "isPrime", "long_name": "isPrime( ll x)", "start_line": 215, "end_line": 233, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 106, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll j , ll maks)", "start_line": 255, "end_line": 291, "parameters": ["j", "maks"], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 77, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 293, "end_line": 317, "parameters": [], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1336.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 305, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41929971", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 272, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1336.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1337.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41919835", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1337.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1338.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 93, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41919524", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 70, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 14, "parameters": [], "filename": "1338.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1339.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 119, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41917057", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int , char **)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["int", "**"], "filename": "1339.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "134.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 272, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45039981", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "134.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 129, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1340.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41904248", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 264, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1340.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1341.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41902824", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1342.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41896894", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1343.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41896191", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 214, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1344.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41886311", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1344.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1345.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 121, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41884888", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1345.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1346.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41878370", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1346.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1347.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41872759", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( unsigned u , unsigned v)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["u", "v"], "filename": "1347.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 64, "parameters": [], "filename": "1347.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1348.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41851110", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1348.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 50, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1349.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 264, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41844212", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 255, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1349.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 46, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "135.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 889, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45037450", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 21, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 90, "name": "getint", "long_name": "getint()", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "getll", "long_name": "getll()", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "getdb", "long_name": "getdb()", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "prln", "long_name": "prln()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "pr", "long_name": "pr( const char * s = \" \")", "start_line": 50, "end_line": 50, "parameters": ["\" \""], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "pr", "long_name": "pr( bool x)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "pr", "long_name": "pr( int x)", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "pr", "long_name": "pr( ll x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "pr", "long_name": "pr( double x)", "start_line": 54, "end_line": 54, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "pr", "long_name": "pr( long double x)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "pr", "long_name": "pr( pair<T,T> x)", "start_line": 56, "end_line": 56, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 63, "name": "pr", "long_name": "pr( T const t [ ] , int len , const char * h = \"\" , const char * c = \"\\n\")", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 58, "parameters": ["]", "len", "\"\"", "\"\\n\""], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "updmax", "long_name": "updmax( T & a , T const & b)", "start_line": 62, "end_line": 62, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "updmin", "long_name": "updmin( T & a , T const & b)", "start_line": 64, "end_line": 64, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "Descr", "long_name": "Descr( T * from , T * to)", "start_line": 66, "end_line": 66, "parameters": ["from", "to"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "LBound", "long_name": "LBound( T * from , T * to , T const & val)", "start_line": 68, "end_line": 68, "parameters": ["from", "to", "val"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "UBound", "long_name": "UBound( T * from , T * to , T const & val)", "start_line": 70, "end_line": 70, "parameters": ["from", "to", "val"], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "TBegin", "long_name": "TBegin()", "start_line": 72, "end_line": 72, "parameters": [], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 69, "name": "TEnd", "long_name": "TEnd( const char * c = \"time: \")", "start_line": 74, "end_line": 80, "parameters": ["\"time: \""], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "TTick", "long_name": "TTick( const char * c = \"time:\")", "start_line": 82, "end_line": 82, "parameters": ["\"time:\""], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 88, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1350.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41815827", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "1350.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1351.cpp", "nloc": 103, "token_count": 358, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41756765", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 76, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "1351.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1352.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41756556", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 246, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1352.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1353.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41751614", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 110, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 89, "name": "find_max_flip", "long_name": "find_max_flip()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1354.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41751382", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 34, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 68, "name": "maxsum", "long_name": "maxsum( int n)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1354.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , const char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 189, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1354.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1355.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41749601", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 34, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , const char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 177, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1355.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1356.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41740832", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1357.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41740709", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "1357.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1358.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41739692", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 121, "name": "flip", "long_name": "flip( int n , int i , int j)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["n", "i", "j"], "filename": "1358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1359.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41736610", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1359.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "136.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 379, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45037392", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 226, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1360.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41734664", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1360.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1361.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41685525", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1361.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1362.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41684169", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1363.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41678740", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1363.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1364.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 312, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41678704", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 46, "name": "Sum", "long_name": "Sum( int An [ ] , int n)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["]", "n"], "filename": "1364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 250, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "1364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1365.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41673468", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1366.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41669837", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1366.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1367.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41668327", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1367.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1368.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 320, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41663063", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 66, "name": "sol", "long_name": "sol( int x , int y)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1368.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1368.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1369.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41647791", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1369.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "137.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45034513", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1370.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 325, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41647366", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 289, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1371.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41643964", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 62, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "1371.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1371.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1372.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 216, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41640749", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 155, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1372.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 9, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1372.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1373.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41631076", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 84, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( string s , int i , int j)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["s", "i", "j"], "filename": "1373.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1373.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1374.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41626809", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1374.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1375.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 304, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41605813", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 276, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1375.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1376.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41599083", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1376.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1377.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41598768", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1377.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1378.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41591454", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 151, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1378.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 12, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1378.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1379.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 342, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41588918", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 19, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1379.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 19, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1379.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 64, "parameters": [], "filename": "1379.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "138.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45034394", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1380.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41579080", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "1380.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1381.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41576797", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1382.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 289, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41576380", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 89, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1382.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1382.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1383.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41574534", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "nhap", "long_name": "nhap()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1383.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 132, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1383.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 54, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1383.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1384.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41572386", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1385.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41565087", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1385.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1386.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 94, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41564569", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 73, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1386.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1387.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41559534", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1388.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 316, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41543908", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 83, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1388.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1388.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( int x)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1388.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1388.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1389.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41541954", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1389.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "139.cpp", "nloc": 5, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45031635", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 11, "parameters": [], "filename": "139.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1390.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41537604", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1390.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1391.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41537451", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1391.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1392.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41537127", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1392.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1393.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41536237", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 23, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "prn", "long_name": "prn( T first)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["first"], "filename": "1393.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 25, "name": "prn", "long_name": "prn( T first , Args ... args)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["first", "args"], "filename": "1393.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "1393.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1394.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41528074", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1394.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1395.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41519560", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "1395.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1396.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41519306", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1396.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1397.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41519262", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1397.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1398.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41507139", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1398.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1399.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41486836", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 151, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1399.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 12, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1399.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "14.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45575030", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "14.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "140.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 272, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45029893", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1400.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41468710", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1400.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1401.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 248, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41463756", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 241, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1401.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1402.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41456297", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1402.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1403.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41447779", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1403.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1404.cpp", "nloc": 87, "token_count": 719, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41443262", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 9, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 24, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 28, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 41, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 34, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 46, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: pair<T1,T2> & p)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 40, "parameters": ["os", "p"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 81, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 90, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: set<T> & v)", "start_line": 58, "end_line": 70, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 94, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: map<T1,T2> & v)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 46, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: unordered_set<T> & v)", "start_line": 88, "end_line": 90, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 50, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: unordered_map<T1,T2> & v)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 126, "parameters": [], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1405.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 309, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41437714", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1405.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1406.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41436374", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1406.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1407.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41432120", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1407.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1408.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41429587", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1408.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1409.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41428291", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1409.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "141.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45029322", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1410.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41427519", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 60, "name": "maxsub", "long_name": "maxsub( ll a [ ] , ll n)", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["]", "n"], "filename": "1410.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "1410.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1411.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41426441", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1411.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1413.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 306, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41424018", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 292, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1413.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1414.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41422340", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 27, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1414.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1415.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41421698", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 54, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1415.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 54, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1416.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41420307", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1416.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 48, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1417.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41418637", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1417.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1418.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41414652", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "1418.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1419.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41414626", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 14, "parameters": [], "filename": "1419.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "142.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45025857", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1420.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41414620", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 14, "parameters": [], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1421.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41411273", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1421.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1422.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 345, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41410078", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 56, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1422.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "1422.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "1422.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1422.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1423.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 309, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41407960", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 297, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 108, "parameters": [], "filename": "1423.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1424.cpp", "nloc": 101, "token_count": 689, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41407711", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 189, "name": "findMin", "long_name": "findMin( int n , int s)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["n", "s"], "filename": "1424.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 189, "name": "findMax", "long_name": "findMax( int n , int s)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["n", "s"], "filename": "1424.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 297, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1424.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1425.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 130, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41401501", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1425.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1426.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41397104", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1426.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1427.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 246, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41396458", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 195, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1427.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1427.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1428.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41391920", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1428.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1429.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41387513", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1429.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "143.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45024048", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 40, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( int a , int b)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 209, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1430.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41386334", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 35, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1431.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41386033", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 35, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1431.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1432.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 353, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41383562", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 62, "token_count": 344, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 193, "parameters": [], "filename": "1432.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 177, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1433.cpp", "nloc": 95, "token_count": 670, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41382786", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 64, "used_headers": 64, "macro_count": 49, "used_macros": 49, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 84, "name": "Read", "long_name": "Read()", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "Write", "long_name": "Write( int x)", "start_line": 148, "end_line": 148, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 64, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 150, "end_line": 150, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcdll", "long_name": "gcdll( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 151, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "itoa", "long_name": "itoa( LL a)", "start_line": 152, "end_line": 152, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "atoi", "long_name": "atoi( string s)", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 170, "parameters": [], "filename": "1433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1434.cpp", "nloc": 95, "token_count": 670, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41382725", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 64, "used_headers": 64, "macro_count": 49, "used_macros": 49, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 84, "name": "Read", "long_name": "Read()", "start_line": 285, "end_line": 293, "parameters": [], "filename": "1434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "Write", "long_name": "Write( int x)", "start_line": 295, "end_line": 295, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 64, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 299, "end_line": 299, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcdll", "long_name": "gcdll( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 301, "end_line": 301, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "itoa", "long_name": "itoa( LL a)", "start_line": 303, "end_line": 303, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "atoi", "long_name": "atoi( string s)", "start_line": 305, "end_line": 305, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 321, "end_line": 339, "parameters": [], "filename": "1434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1435.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41382536", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1435.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1436.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41381635", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "1436.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1437.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41381617", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "1437.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1438.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41381080", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1439.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41379350", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "144.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45022113", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1440.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41379216", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1440.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1441.cpp", "nloc": 148, "token_count": 848, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41338778", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 13, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 64, "name": "prime", "long_name": "prime( lli n)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 32, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( lli n , lli m)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 91, "parameters": ["n", "m"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( lli n , lli m , lli k)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["n", "m", "k"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( lli n , lli m)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["n", "m"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact( lli n)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 33, "name": "sumdigit", "long_name": "sumdigit( int n)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 48, "name": "tobinary", "long_name": "tobinary( int n)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 31, "name": "tostring", "long_name": "tostring( double n)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 171, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 31, "name": "tochar", "long_name": "tochar( int n)", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 187, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 95, "name": "div", "long_name": "div( lli n)", "start_line": 189, "end_line": 217, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "fun", "long_name": "fun( lli n)", "start_line": 219, "end_line": 223, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 156, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( string s1 , string s2)", "start_line": 225, "end_line": 263, "parameters": ["s1", "s2"], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 267, "end_line": 327, "parameters": [], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1442.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41337929", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 262, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1442.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1443.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41337447", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1443.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1444.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41336142", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1444.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1445.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41336129", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1445.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1446.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41334701", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 48, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( int x , int y)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1446.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1446.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1447.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41334628", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1448.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41334582", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1448.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1449.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41334451", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1449.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "145.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45022028", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "145.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1450.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41334440", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 151, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1450.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 12, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1450.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1451.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41334427", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1451.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1453.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 145, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333687", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "1453.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1454.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 383, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333677", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 103, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1454.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 39, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1454.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( int a , int b)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1454.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1454.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1455.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333655", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1455.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1456.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333658", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 219, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1456.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1457.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333597", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1457.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1458.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333580", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1458.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1459.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333573", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1459.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "146.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45020086", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "146.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1460.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333549", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1460.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1461.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 145, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333545", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1461.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1462.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333526", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1462.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1463.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333515", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1463.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1464.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333495", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1464.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1465.cpp", "nloc": 102, "token_count": 674, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333493", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 64, "used_headers": 64, "macro_count": 49, "used_macros": 49, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 84, "name": "Read", "long_name": "Read()", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1465.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "Write", "long_name": "Write( int x)", "start_line": 148, "end_line": 148, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1465.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 64, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 150, "end_line": 150, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1465.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcdll", "long_name": "gcdll( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 151, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1465.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "itoa", "long_name": "itoa( LL a)", "start_line": 152, "end_line": 152, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1465.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "atoi", "long_name": "atoi( string s)", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1465.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 178, "parameters": [], "filename": "1465.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1466.cpp", "nloc": 102, "token_count": 674, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333485", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 64, "used_headers": 64, "macro_count": 49, "used_macros": 49, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 84, "name": "Read", "long_name": "Read()", "start_line": 285, "end_line": 293, "parameters": [], "filename": "1466.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "Write", "long_name": "Write( int x)", "start_line": 295, "end_line": 295, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1466.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 64, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 299, "end_line": 299, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1466.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcdll", "long_name": "gcdll( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 301, "end_line": 301, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1466.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "itoa", "long_name": "itoa( LL a)", "start_line": 303, "end_line": 303, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1466.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "atoi", "long_name": "atoi( string s)", "start_line": 305, "end_line": 305, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1466.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 321, "end_line": 355, "parameters": [], "filename": "1466.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1467.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333473", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1467.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1468.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333465", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1468.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1469.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333463", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 29, "name": "fun", "long_name": "fun()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 17, "parameters": [], "filename": "1469.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1469.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "147.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44990325", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 240, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "147.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1470.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333457", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1470.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1471.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333429", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1471.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1472.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333424", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1473.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41333422", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1473.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1474.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41309797", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1474.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1475.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41308466", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 229, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1475.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1476.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41308417", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 9, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 75, "name": "maxsubset", "long_name": "maxsubset( vector<int> all , int ress)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["all", "ress"], "filename": "1476.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1476.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1477.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41307327", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1477.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1478.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41305228", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 234, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char ** argv)", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["argc", "argv"], "filename": "1478.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1479.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 114, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41302387", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1479.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "148.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44985960", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1480.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 103, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41298464", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1480.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1481.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 226, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41297575", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 203, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1481.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1482.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41291679", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 41, "name": "convert", "long_name": "convert( int a , int b)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1482.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "1482.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1483.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41286403", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1483.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1484.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 246, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41286393", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1484.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1485.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 238, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41286229", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1485.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1486.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41285908", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "1486.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1487.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41284331", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1487.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1488.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41283238", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "1488.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 163, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1489.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41277305", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 66, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ve<int> v , int k)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["v", "k"], "filename": "1489.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 74, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1489.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "149.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 345, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44970035", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 336, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1490.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41276674", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1490.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1491.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41276390", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 113, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ve<int> v , int k)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["v", "k"], "filename": "1491.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "1491.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1493.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41261628", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 164, "name": "solve::solve", "long_name": "solve::solve()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 50, "name": "solve::cnt_one", "long_name": "solve::cnt_one( ve<int> v , int a , int b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["v", "a", "b"], "filename": "1493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 11, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1494.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 226, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41256303", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1494.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1495.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41253925", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1495.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1496.cpp", "nloc": 7, "token_count": 81, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41247442", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 59, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 13, "parameters": [], "filename": "1496.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1497.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41246763", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1497.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1498.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 321, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41240562", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 54, "name": "countones", "long_name": "countones( vector<int> & v , int i , int j)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["v", "i", "j"], "filename": "1498.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 54, "name": "countzero", "long_name": "countzero( vector<int> & v , int i , int j)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["v", "i", "j"], "filename": "1498.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 141, "name": "maxones", "long_name": "maxones( vector<int> & v , int n)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["v", "n"], "filename": "1498.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1498.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1499.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41227517", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1499.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "15.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45569014", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "15.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "150.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 547, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44968194", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 80, "name": "modexpo", "long_name": "modexpo( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "intpoint", "long_name": "intpoint( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "isvalid", "long_name": "isvalid( ll x , ll y , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x", "y", "n", "m"], "filename": "150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 286, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1500.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41223808", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 203, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1500.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1501.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41219539", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1502.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41218472", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1502.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1503.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41208452", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 215, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1503.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1504.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41203076", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 265, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1504.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 113, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1505.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 255, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41201797", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1505.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1506.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41201224", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1506.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1507.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41198696", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1507.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1508.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 369, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41165702", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 349, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1508.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1509.cpp", "nloc": 69, "token_count": 302, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41156998", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "15700 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 20, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( ll x)", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1509.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 53, "name": "expo", "long_name": "expo( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1509.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 203, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1509.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 48, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "151.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44967878", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "151.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1510.cpp", "nloc": 68, "token_count": 293, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41154382", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 23, "used_headers": 18, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 219, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "1510.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1511.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41154136", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1511.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1512.cpp", "nloc": 129, "token_count": 760, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41152653", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 43, "name": "scan_array", "long_name": "scan_array( int n)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 42, "name": "is_prime", "long_name": "is_prime( int x)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 33, "name": "digits_sum", "long_name": "digits_sum( int n)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 48, "name": "digits_sum", "long_name": "digits_sum( string s)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 73, "name": "convert_from_decimal", "long_name": "convert_from_decimal( int num , int base)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["num", "base"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 122, "name": "convert_to_decimal", "long_name": "convert_to_decimal( string str , int base)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 167, "parameters": ["str", "base"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 71, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( int a , int b)", "start_line": 171, "end_line": 195, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 34, "name": "is_palindrome", "long_name": "is_palindrome( string s)", "start_line": 199, "end_line": 209, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 35, "name": "factorial", "long_name": "factorial( int n)", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 225, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 33, "name": "compare::operator ( )", "long_name": "compare::operator ( )( const std :: string & first , const std :: string & second)", "start_line": 231, "end_line": 235, "parameters": ["first", "second"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( int l , int s)", "start_line": 241, "end_line": 247, "parameters": ["l", "s"], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 251, "end_line": 295, "parameters": [], "filename": "1512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1513.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41134321", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1513.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1514.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 105, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41119360", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1514.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1515.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41116665", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 51, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 116, "parameters": [], "filename": "1515.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 48, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1516.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 316, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41113371", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 91, "name": "mid", "long_name": "mid( int st , int ed , int n)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["st", "ed", "n"], "filename": "1516.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1516.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1517.cpp", "nloc": 71, "token_count": 374, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41109727", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 33, "name": "Compare", "long_name": "Compare( const pair<int,int> & a , const pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1517.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 29, "name": "tostring", "long_name": "tostring( ll Number)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["Number"], "filename": "1517.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 26, "name": "toint", "long_name": "toint( string String)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["String"], "filename": "1517.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 250, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 215, "parameters": [], "filename": "1517.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 95, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1518.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 382, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41096962", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "1518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1519.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41093082", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "1519.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "152.cpp", "nloc": 71, "token_count": 405, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44964114", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 15, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 82, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( int v)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 189, "parameters": [], "filename": "152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1520.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 114, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41064358", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1520.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1521.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41062599", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1521.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1522.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41039598", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1523.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41024588", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1523.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1524.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/41008250", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 48, "name": "count", "long_name": "count( string s , char x)", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["s", "x"], "filename": "1524.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 57, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( vector<ll> a)", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1524.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "1524.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1525.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40989816", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1525.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1526.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40989727", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 6, "name": "none", "long_name": "none( ...)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["..."], "filename": "1526.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1526.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1527.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40989095", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1527.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1528.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 293, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40984657", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 284, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1528.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1529.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40982030", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1529.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "153.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44963696", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1530.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 91, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40976869", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 64, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1530.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1531.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40972958", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1531.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1532.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 282, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40972420", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 33, "name": "calcSum", "long_name": "calcSum( const vector<int> & v)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1532.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 85, "name": "invert", "long_name": "invert( vector<int> v , int a , int b)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["v", "a", "b"], "filename": "1532.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1532.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1533.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 480, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40963081", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "97300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 19, "name": "so", "long_name": "so( string a , string b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1533.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1533.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1534.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40935438", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1534.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1535.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40933870", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1535.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1536.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40933855", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 258, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1536.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1537.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40929342", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1537.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1538.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40929084", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1538.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1539.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40928126", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1539.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "154.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44961824", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "154.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1540.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 293, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40927894", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 286, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1541.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 109, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40927739", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1541.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1542.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 95, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40923794", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 88, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1542.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1543.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40920471", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1543.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1544.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40920238", "exec_time": "122 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 37, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1544.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1545.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 509, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40918386", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 86, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1545.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 103, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read( mitsuha & x)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1545.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "chtholly::write", "long_name": "chtholly::write( mitsuha x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1545.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "chtholly::fuhao", "long_name": "chtholly::fuhao()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1545.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1545.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1546.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 279, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40915327", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 246, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "1546.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1547.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40915015", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "1547.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1548.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40914982", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1548.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1549.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 509, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40914834", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 86, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read()", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 17, "parameters": [], "filename": "1549.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 103, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read( mitsuha & x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1549.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "chtholly::write", "long_name": "chtholly::write( mitsuha x)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 34, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1549.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "chtholly::fuhao", "long_name": "chtholly::fuhao()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1549.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1549.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "155.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44961727", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 22, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "155.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1550.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40912826", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1550.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1551.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40901017", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char ** argv)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["argc", "argv"], "filename": "1551.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1552.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40887489", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1552.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1553.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40881699", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 35, "name": "flp", "long_name": "flp( int i , int j)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "1553.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1553.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1554.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 258, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40867787", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 72, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int ind)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["ind"], "filename": "1554.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1554.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1555.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40865560", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1555.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1556.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40841599", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 59, "token_count": 263, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1556.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 117, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1557.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 328, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40836534", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 321, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1557.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1558.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 145, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40828604", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1558.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1559.cpp", "nloc": 83, "token_count": 409, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40816547", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 22, "nloc": 81, "token_count": 402, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "1559.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 161, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "156.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44960244", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "156.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1560.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40813658", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "1560.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1561.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40812729", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 40, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1562.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40807128", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1562.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1563.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40776455", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1563.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1564.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40756843", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1564.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1565.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 258, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40744841", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 251, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1565.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1566.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40744362", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1566.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1567.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40736626", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "1567.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1568.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40733708", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1568.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1569.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40730824", "exec_time": "60 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1569.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "157.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 393, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44954595", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 75, "token_count": 386, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 191, "parameters": [], "filename": "157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 187, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1570.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40727833", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1570.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1571.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40725244", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1571.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1572.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40708683", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 100, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1572.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 61, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1572.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1573.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40689854", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1573.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1574.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40689784", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1574.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1575.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 459, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40681696", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "20400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "ceil1", "long_name": "ceil1( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1575.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b , ll n)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["a", "b", "n"], "filename": "1575.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 48, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( ll u)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["u"], "filename": "1575.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "1575.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1576.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/327/submission/40678390", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1576.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1577.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45696833", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 62, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( string s1 , string s2)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["s1", "s2"], "filename": "1577.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 65, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1577.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1578.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45693284", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1578.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1579.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45693175", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 316, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1579.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "158.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44952812", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1580.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45693169", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 316, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "1580.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 46, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1581.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45693115", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 316, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1581.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1582.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45693072", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 296, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1582.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1583.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45671789", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1583.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1584.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 318, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45671146", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "48200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1584.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1585.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 332, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45666963", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 54, "token_count": 325, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1585.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1586.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 360, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45666334", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 54, "token_count": 336, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1586.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1587.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 328, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45665979", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 23, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 271, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 58, "parameters": [], "filename": "1587.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 42, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1588.cpp", "nloc": 99, "token_count": 931, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45660267", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 13, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 5, "name": "Point::Point", "long_name": "Point::Point()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "Point::Point", "long_name": "Point::Point( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "Point::operator -", "long_name": "Point::operator -( const Point & a) const", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "Point::operator <", "long_name": "Point::operator <( const Point & a) const", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 32, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 47, "name": "qpow", "long_name": "qpow( ull a , ull b)", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "AC_Automata::clear", "long_name": "AC_Automata::clear()", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "AC_Automata::idx", "long_name": "AC_Automata::idx( char c)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 117, "name": "AC_Automata::insert", "long_name": "AC_Automata::insert( char * s , int l , int v)", "start_line": 50, "end_line": 62, "parameters": ["s", "l", "v"], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 207, "name": "AC_Automata::build", "long_name": "AC_Automata::build()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 85, "name": "AC_Automata::find", "long_name": "AC_Automata::find( char * s , int l)", "start_line": 82, "end_line": 90, "parameters": ["s", "l"], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 37, "name": "AC_Automata::print", "long_name": "AC_Automata::print( int j)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 96, "parameters": ["j"], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 154, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 100, "end_line": 112, "parameters": [], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 17, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 118, "parameters": [], "filename": "1588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1589.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 292, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45652126", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 62, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & out , vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "1589.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1589.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "159.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44952765", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1591.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 409, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45643106", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 332, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1591.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 48, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1592.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 236, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45623161", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 223, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1592.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1593.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 236, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45622782", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 223, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1593.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1594.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45583756", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1594.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1595.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45582725", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 250, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1595.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1596.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45580982", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1596.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1597.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45577036", "exec_time": "1840 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 116, "name": "find_pattern", "long_name": "find_pattern( string s , string p)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["s", "p"], "filename": "1597.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1597.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1598.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 130, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45571915", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1598.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1599.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 463, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45570401", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 44, "nloc": 62, "token_count": 456, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1599.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 127, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "16.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45550383", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "16.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "160.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44947146", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1600.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45567494", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1600.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1601.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45567217", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 342, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1601.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 115, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1602.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45563050", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1602.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1603.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 262, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45561639", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 217, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1603.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1604.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 113, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45561337", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1604.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1605.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 362, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45560326", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 27, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 359, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1605.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1606.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 315, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45555428", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 256, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "1606.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 35, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 175, "parameters": [], "filename": "1606.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1607.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45555038", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 175, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1607.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 35, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "1607.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1608.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 410, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45554724", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 351, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 177, "parameters": [], "filename": "1608.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 117, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 35, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 183, "end_line": 203, "parameters": [], "filename": "1608.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1609.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 275, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45510394", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1609.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "161.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44937423", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "161.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1610.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45504363", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 219, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1610.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1611.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 428, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45504047", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "12300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 177, "name": "for1", "long_name": "for1( string m)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1611.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 177, "name": "for2", "long_name": "for2( string s)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1611.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 44, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1611.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1612.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45500111", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1612.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1613.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45499896", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1613.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1614.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 310, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45494007", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 24, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 303, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1614.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1615.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45493344", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1615.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1616.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 216, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45492526", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "rev", "long_name": "rev( long long l , long long r)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1616.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 75, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( string a , string b)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1616.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 63, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1616.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1617.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45485978", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 294, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1617.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1618.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45484103", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1618.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1619.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 100, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45479309", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1619.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "162.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44935489", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "162.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1620.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45468792", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1620.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1621.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45457389", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 223, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 68, "parameters": [], "filename": "1621.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1622.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 313, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45447043", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 258, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1622.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1623.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 255, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45444881", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 201, "name": "fun", "long_name": "fun( string s)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1623.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 46, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1623.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1624.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 260, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45437839", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 231, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1624.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1625.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45437107", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 256, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1625.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1626.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45432388", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 70, "token_count": 315, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1626.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 141, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1627.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45432429", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 70, "token_count": 315, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1627.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 141, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1628.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 331, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45432399", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 324, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 58, "parameters": [], "filename": "1628.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 56, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1629.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 364, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45432024", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 28, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 357, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1629.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 119, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "163.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44929897", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 273, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "163.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1630.cpp", "nloc": 9, "token_count": 92, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45430507", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 85, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "1630.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1631.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45418540", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1631.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1632.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 337, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45416957", "exec_time": "1466 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 304, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1632.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1633.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45392770", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 16, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1633.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1634.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 353, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45373133", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 0, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 63, "name": "upper", "long_name": "upper( int x)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1634.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 68, "name": "lower", "long_name": "lower( int x)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1634.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1634.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1635.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 353, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45373074", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 0, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 63, "name": "upper", "long_name": "upper( int x)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1635.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 68, "name": "lower", "long_name": "lower( int x)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1635.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1635.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1636.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 298, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45329901", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 230, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1636.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1637.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 274, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45319912", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1637.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1638.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45306684", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "ye", "long_name": "ye()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "1638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1639.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45283368", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1639.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "164.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 268, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44929427", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "164.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1640.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 226, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45276156", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1640.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1641.cpp", "nloc": 10, "token_count": 112, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45260320", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 10, "parameters": [], "filename": "1641.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1642.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45250131", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1642.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1643.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45246240", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1643.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1644.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45241884", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1644.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1645.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 536, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45217604", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 32, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll a , ll b , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "fpow", "long_name": "fpow( ll n , ll k , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["n", "k", "mod"], "filename": "1645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll a , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["a", "mod"], "filename": "1645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "sa", "long_name": "sa( const pair<int,int> & a , const pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "fd", "long_name": "fd( const pair<int,int> & a , const pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "sd", "long_name": "sd( const pair<int,int> & a , const pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 276, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "1645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1646.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45210661", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int x , int y)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1646.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 29, "name": "lif", "long_name": "lif( float x)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1646.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 205, "parameters": [], "filename": "1646.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1647.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45197456", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 94, "name": "binserch", "long_name": "binserch( vector<int> arr , int l , int r , int x)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["arr", "l", "r", "x"], "filename": "1647.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 39, "name": "issimp", "long_name": "issimp( int a)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1647.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 44, "name": "delit", "long_name": "delit( long x)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1647.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1647.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1648.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45178189", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1648.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1649.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45168944", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 285, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1649.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "165.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44926770", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "165.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1650.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 389, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45166314", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 21, "used_headers": 6, "macro_count": 26, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll b , ll y)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["b", "y"], "filename": "1650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll b , ll y)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["b", "y"], "filename": "1650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "dis", "long_name": "dis( double x1 , double x2 , double y1 , double y2)", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["x1", "x2", "y1", "y2"], "filename": "1650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "random", "long_name": "random( double start , double en)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["start", "en"], "filename": "1650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 88, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1651.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45164566", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 141, "parameters": [], "filename": "1651.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1652.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45160942", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1652.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1653.cpp", "nloc": 68, "token_count": 308, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45158188", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 66, "token_count": 301, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "1653.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 131, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1654.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45141284", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "1654.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1655.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 258, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45138304", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 30, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 182, "name": "yolosmile", "long_name": "yolosmile()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1655.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 65, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "1655.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1656.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45132720", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 280, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1656.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1657.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 126, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45128235", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1657.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1658.cpp", "nloc": 61, "token_count": 722, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45123935", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 48, "nloc": 57, "token_count": 709, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1658.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 113, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1659.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45107417", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 58, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( string s , string a , string b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["s", "a", "b"], "filename": "1659.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 70, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1659.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "166.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44925749", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1660.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45099482", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 289, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1660.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1661.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45096430", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1661.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1662.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 283, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45084807", "exec_time": "1107 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 234, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 104, "parameters": [], "filename": "1662.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1663.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45072625", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1663.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1664.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 336, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45072393", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 25, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 329, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1664.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1665.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 308, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45066559", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 271, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1665.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1666.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 312, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45059536", "exec_time": "1560 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 41, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 33, "name": "bysec", "long_name": "bysec( const pair<ll,ll> & a , const pair<ll,ll> & b)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1666.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "strfind", "long_name": "strfind( string & st , string & s)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["st", "s"], "filename": "1666.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 209, "parameters": [], "filename": "1666.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1667.cpp", "nloc": 78, "token_count": 625, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45057359", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1667.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 41, "nloc": 55, "token_count": 472, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 197, "parameters": [], "filename": "1667.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1668.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 350, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44990959", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 24, "nloc": 61, "token_count": 339, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1668.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 125, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1669.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 487, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44981260", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 80, "name": "modexpo", "long_name": "modexpo( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1669.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "intpoint", "long_name": "intpoint( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "1669.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "isvalid", "long_name": "isvalid( ll x , ll y , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x", "y", "n", "m"], "filename": "1669.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "1669.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "167.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44924296", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "167.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1670.cpp", "nloc": 11, "token_count": 97, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44975782", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 90, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "1670.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1671.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44964760", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 250, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1671.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1672.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44958013", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1672.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1673.cpp", "nloc": 10, "token_count": 94, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44949460", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "1673.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1674.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44936869", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1674.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1675.cpp", "nloc": 7, "token_count": 91, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44916825", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 15, "parameters": [], "filename": "1675.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1676.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 354, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44916774", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 22, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 349, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1677.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 131, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44916050", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1677.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1678.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44915529", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1678.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1679.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44905034", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1679.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "168.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44922684", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1680.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44879879", "exec_time": "1450 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1680.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 40, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1681.cpp", "nloc": 78, "token_count": 388, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44838078", "exec_time": "1575 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 73, "token_count": 364, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1681.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 96, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1682.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44820003", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1682.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1683.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44767210", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1683.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1684.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 325, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44766835", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 318, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 54, "parameters": [], "filename": "1684.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 52, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1685.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 297, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44757473", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 23, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 290, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1685.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 95, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1686.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44757430", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 264, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1686.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1687.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 352, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44750777", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 38, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( string s)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1687.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 43, "name": "isvowel", "long_name": "isvowel( char c)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "1687.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 49, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( pair<int,int> & a , pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1687.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 169, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1687.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 34, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "1687.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1688.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44750490", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "8200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1688.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1689.cpp", "nloc": 74, "token_count": 374, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44740538", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 29, "nloc": 67, "token_count": 354, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1689.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "169.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 225, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44921406", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1690.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44721732", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1690.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1691.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44715319", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1691.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1692.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 310, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44708256", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 303, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1692.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1693.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 341, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44699323", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 147, "name": "checab", "long_name": "checab( string s)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1693.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 147, "name": "checba", "long_name": "checba( string s)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1693.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 35, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1693.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1694.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 103, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44662093", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1694.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1695.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44620467", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( int a , int b)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1695.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 289, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1695.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1696.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 324, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44606528", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 315, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1696.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1697.cpp", "nloc": 9, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44598627", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "1697.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1698.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44573855", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1698.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1699.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 339, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44551530", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 63, "token_count": 330, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "1699.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 143, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "17.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45509715", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "17.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "170.cpp", "nloc": 93, "token_count": 703, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44913448", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 68, "name": "edmonds_karp::edmonds_karp", "long_name": "edmonds_karp::edmonds_karp( int _n , int _st , int _fin)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["_n", "_st", "_fin"], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 45, "name": "edmonds_karp::add_edge", "long_name": "edmonds_karp::add_edge( int from , int to , T c = 1)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["from", "to", "1"], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 168, "name": "edmonds_karp::expath", "long_name": "edmonds_karp::expath( vector<int> & pr)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["pr"], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 95, "name": "edmonds_karp::max_flow", "long_name": "edmonds_karp::max_flow()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 278, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 215, "parameters": [], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1700.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44533585", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1700.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1701.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44533437", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1701.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1702.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 347, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44522204", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 26, "nloc": 63, "token_count": 340, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1702.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 127, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1703.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 260, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44519832", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 247, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1703.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 40, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1704.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44485763", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "1704.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1705.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44476450", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 23, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 271, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1705.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1706.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44471781", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1706.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1707.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44462907", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 238, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1707.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1708.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 103, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44461826", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 15, "parameters": [], "filename": "1708.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1709.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44457930", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 13, "parameters": [], "filename": "1709.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "171.cpp", "nloc": 93, "token_count": 703, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44913344", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 68, "name": "edmonds_karp::edmonds_karp", "long_name": "edmonds_karp::edmonds_karp( int _n , int _st , int _fin)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["_n", "_st", "_fin"], "filename": "171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 45, "name": "edmonds_karp::add_edge", "long_name": "edmonds_karp::add_edge( int from , int to , T c = 1)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["from", "to", "1"], "filename": "171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 168, "name": "edmonds_karp::expath", "long_name": "edmonds_karp::expath( vector<int> & pr)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["pr"], "filename": "171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 95, "name": "edmonds_karp::max_flow", "long_name": "edmonds_karp::max_flow()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 278, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 215, "parameters": [], "filename": "171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1710.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 248, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44454587", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 239, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1710.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1711.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 342, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44419447", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 146, "name": "check1", "long_name": "check1()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1711.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 146, "name": "check2", "long_name": "check2()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "1711.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 31, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "1711.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1712.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44411294", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1712.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1713.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44388260", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "1713.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1714.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 530, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44380135", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 74, "token_count": 521, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "1714.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 149, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1715.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 274, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44375604", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 267, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "1715.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1716.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44370304", "exec_time": "1123 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1716.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1717.cpp", "nloc": 82, "token_count": 370, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44367628", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 29, "nloc": 77, "token_count": 348, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "1717.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 153, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1718.cpp", "nloc": 79, "token_count": 520, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44365094", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 29, "nloc": 77, "token_count": 513, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "1718.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 155, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1719.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44364343", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1719.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "172.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 338, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44912467", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 331, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1720.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 509, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44343999", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 29, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "on_bit", "long_name": "on_bit( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "off_bit", "long_name": "off_bit( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "is_on_bit", "long_name": "is_on_bit( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "flip_bit", "long_name": "flip_bit( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "lsb", "long_name": "lsb( int x)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "on_bit_all", "long_name": "on_bit_all( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "1720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1721.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 254, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44330479", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 239, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1721.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1722.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44311351", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 283, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1722.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1723.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44281847", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 274, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1723.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1724.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 493, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44280002", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 38, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 470, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "1724.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1725.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44268429", "exec_time": "1341 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "1725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 40, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1726.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44268169", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1726.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1727.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44260016", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1727.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1728.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 365, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44236970", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 13, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 270, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 80, "parameters": [], "filename": "1728.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1729.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 311, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44227026", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1729.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "173.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44912441", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "173.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1730.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44226480", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1730.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1731.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44223303", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1731.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1732.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44180475", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 6, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1732.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1733.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44171981", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1733.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1734.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44115411", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 287, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1734.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 119, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1735.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 248, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44114126", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1735.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1736.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44076847", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1736.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1737.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 248, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44050907", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 241, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1737.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1738.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 381, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44038227", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 12, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 204, "name": "myc", "long_name": "myc( string s)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1738.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 50, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1738.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1739.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44033483", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1739.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "174.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44912072", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 236, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "174.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1740.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44026736", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 66, "name": "findss", "long_name": "findss( int pos)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["pos"], "filename": "1740.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1740.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1741.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44023298", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 236, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char ** argv)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["argc", "argv"], "filename": "1741.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1742.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44022950", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 175, "name": "get_answer", "long_name": "get_answer( string s)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1742.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 24, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1742.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1743.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44012322", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 287, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 66, "parameters": [], "filename": "1743.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 60, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1744.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44012293", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 287, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 66, "parameters": [], "filename": "1744.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 60, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1745.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44011150", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 22, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 294, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1745.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 52, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1746.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 268, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44010643", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 259, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 185, "parameters": [], "filename": "1746.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 131, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1747.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44000493", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 60, "token_count": 289, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1747.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 121, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1748.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43998580", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1748.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1749.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43993721", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1749.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "175.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44908927", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "175.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 95, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1750.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43978084", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1750.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1751.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43946414", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 198, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1751.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 15, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 179, "parameters": [], "filename": "1751.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1752.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43943317", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 117, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( string s , int k)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["s", "k"], "filename": "1752.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 53, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1752.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1753.cpp", "nloc": 11, "token_count": 92, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43938230", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 11, "parameters": [], "filename": "1753.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1754.cpp", "nloc": 76, "token_count": 371, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43937092", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "8400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 77, "name": "pe", "long_name": "pe( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1754.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "1754.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1755.cpp", "nloc": 76, "token_count": 371, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43937085", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "8400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 77, "name": "pe", "long_name": "pe( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1755.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 80, "parameters": [], "filename": "1755.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1756.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43929051", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1756.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1758.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43928137", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "1758.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1759.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43924116", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "1759.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "176.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 292, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44903986", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "176.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1760.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 275, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43924033", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 250, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1760.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1761.cpp", "nloc": 85, "token_count": 363, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43923691", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 81, "token_count": 347, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1761.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 86, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1762.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 353, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43923671", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 313, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "1762.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 46, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1763.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 370, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43923645", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 22, "nloc": 75, "token_count": 363, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1763.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1764.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43923307", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 256, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "1764.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1765.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 347, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43923162", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 299, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1765.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1766.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 238, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43923142", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 231, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "1766.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1767.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43922940", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "1767.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1768.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43922865", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1768.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1769.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43922861", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 254, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1769.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "177.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44902503", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "177.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1770.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 348, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43913616", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 50, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 61, "token_count": 341, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 78, "end_line": 153, "parameters": [], "filename": "1770.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 76, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1771.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 336, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43823874", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "no", "long_name": "no()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 7, "parameters": [], "filename": "1771.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "yes", "long_name": "yes()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 10, "parameters": [], "filename": "1771.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 279, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "1771.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1772.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43817781", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1772.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1773.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43802486", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1773.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1774.cpp", "nloc": 71, "token_count": 322, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43797056", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "findAB", "long_name": "findAB( char a , char b)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1774.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "findBA", "long_name": "findBA( char a , char b)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1774.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 58, "token_count": 253, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "1774.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 143, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1775.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 121, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43794316", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1775.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1776.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43746030", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 241, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1776.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1777.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43744739", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 191, "name": "poss", "long_name": "poss( string s)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1777.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 43, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1777.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1778.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43731426", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1778.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1779.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43730388", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1779.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "178.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44898991", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "178.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1780.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43730311", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 19, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 26, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "debug", "long_name": "debug( int n , ...)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["n", "..."], "filename": "1780.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 199, "end_line": 237, "parameters": [], "filename": "1780.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1781.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 293, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43725997", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "fastio", "long_name": "fastio()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 15, "parameters": [], "filename": "1781.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 259, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1781.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1782.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43715864", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1782.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1783.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 98, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43711272", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "1783.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1784.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 289, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43710710", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 25, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 276, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1784.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1785.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43705348", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "1785.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1786.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 131, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43698435", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "1786.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1787.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43696800", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 256, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1787.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1788.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43691074", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 232, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( string s)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 40, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1788.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 29, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1788.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1789.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 268, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43690245", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 250, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1789.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "179.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44896679", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1790.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43689829", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 57, "token_count": 264, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 62, "parameters": [], "filename": "1790.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1791.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43689784", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 57, "token_count": 264, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 62, "parameters": [], "filename": "1791.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1792.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43689278", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1792.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1793.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 272, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43683998", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 215, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "1793.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1794.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43683954", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 239, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1794.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1795.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 268, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43683824", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 22, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 253, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1795.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1796.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43683771", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "1796.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1797.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 236, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43670786", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "done", "long_name": "done()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 12, "parameters": [], "filename": "1797.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "1797.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1798.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 495, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43667267", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 30, "nloc": 63, "token_count": 461, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "1798.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 125, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1799.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 581, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43661392", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 42, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const pair<A,B> & p)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "1799.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 67, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const vector<A> & v)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "1799.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 51, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( const string & s , char c)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "1799.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "1799.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 61, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "1799.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "1799.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "18.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45509633", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "4800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 147, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int p , int q , int flag)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["p", "q", "flag"], "filename": "18.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "18.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "180.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44895549", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "180.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1800.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43652049", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1800.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1801.cpp", "nloc": 98, "token_count": 558, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43649604", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 65, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1801.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "BINARY_SEARCH", "long_name": "BINARY_SEARCH( ll dp [ ] , ll n , ll key)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["]", "n", "key"], "filename": "1801.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 55, "name": "CONVERT_TO_BINARY", "long_name": "CONVERT_TO_BINARY( ll s)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1801.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 55, "name": "PALIN", "long_name": "PALIN( string s)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1801.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 53, "name": "STOI", "long_name": "STOI( string s)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1801.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 20, "name": "modInverse", "long_name": "modInverse( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "1801.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 214, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 249, "parameters": [], "filename": "1801.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1802.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43649573", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1802.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1803.cpp", "nloc": 70, "token_count": 385, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43632384", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 27, "nloc": 68, "token_count": 380, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1803.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 143, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1804.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43628548", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1804.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1805.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43625351", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "1805.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1806.cpp", "nloc": 81, "token_count": 502, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43615104", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 37, "nloc": 79, "token_count": 495, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "1806.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 159, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1807.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43593282", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1807.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1808.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 444, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43585316", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 62, "token_count": 437, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1808.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 123, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1809.cpp", "nloc": 105, "token_count": 650, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43577860", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 59, "token_count": 337, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1809.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "modInv", "long_name": "modInv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 86, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "1809.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 88, "end_line": 98, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "1809.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "mpower", "long_name": "mpower( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 100, "end_line": 112, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "1809.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 51, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 114, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1809.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "181.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44895119", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1810.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43572169", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1810.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1811.cpp", "nloc": 111, "token_count": 530, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43554581", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 85, "name": "isPrime", "long_name": "isPrime( ll n)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1811.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 77, "name": "seive", "long_name": "seive()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1811.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1811.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 55, "token_count": 240, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 257, "parameters": [], "filename": "1811.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 261, "end_line": 305, "parameters": [], "filename": "1811.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1812.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 460, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43550308", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 33, "name": "update", "long_name": "update( int i , int val)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["i", "val"], "filename": "1812.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 45, "name": "query", "long_name": "query( int i)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "1812.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 77, "name": "kmpPreprocess", "long_name": "kmpPreprocess( string P)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["P"], "filename": "1812.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 115, "name": "kmpSearch", "long_name": "kmpSearch( string T , string P , bool f)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["T", "P", "f"], "filename": "1812.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 205, "parameters": [], "filename": "1812.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1813.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43542005", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1813.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1814.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43541952", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 67, "name": "buscar", "long_name": "buscar( string str , string s1 , string s2)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["str", "s1", "s2"], "filename": "1814.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1814.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1815.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43540408", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 70, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( string input , string a , string b)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["input", "a", "b"], "filename": "1815.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 58, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1815.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1816.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43518914", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1816.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1817.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43516113", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "1817.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1818.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43516105", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1818.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1819.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43508246", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1819.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "182.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44889726", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "182.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1820.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43507289", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1820.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1821.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43506377", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1821.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1822.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43506356", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1822.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1823.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43502666", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "1823.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1824.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43501343", "exec_time": "1794 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1824.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1825.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43500776", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 324, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1825.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1826.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 254, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43500591", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 243, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1826.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1827.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 334, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43500540", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 329, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1827.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1828.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 275, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43500440", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 260, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "1828.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 50, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1829.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43499413", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 18, "parameters": [], "filename": "1829.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "183.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44886081", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1830.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43499016", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1830.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1831.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43484395", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 110, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1831.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1832.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 288, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43479354", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 281, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1832.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1833.cpp", "nloc": 81, "token_count": 465, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43465507", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 24, "nloc": 79, "token_count": 458, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 161, "parameters": [], "filename": "1833.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 157, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1834.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43464958", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1834.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1835.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 352, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43453485", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 251, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1835.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1836.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43451604", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1836.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1837.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43416232", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 98, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1837.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1838.cpp", "nloc": 9, "token_count": 112, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43416131", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 17, "parameters": [], "filename": "1838.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1839.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43412125", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 18, "parameters": [], "filename": "1839.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "184.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44883216", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "184.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1840.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43411732", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1840.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1841.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43411172", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1841.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1842.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 315, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43384435", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 68, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1842.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 75, "name": "check1", "long_name": "check1( string s)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 60, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1842.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 75, "name": "check2", "long_name": "check2( string s)", "start_line": 62, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1842.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1843.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43361766", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 237, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1843.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1844.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 419, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43352679", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 97, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( Drake & x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1844.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 47, "name": "write", "long_name": "write( Drake x)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1844.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( Drake x)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1844.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 10, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1844.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1844.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1845.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43345489", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1845.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1846.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43287279", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1846.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1847.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 94, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43284283", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1847.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1848.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 283, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43271992", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 19, "name": "ReadInt", "long_name": "ReadInt()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1848.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 14, "name": "Print", "long_name": "Print( int t)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["t"], "filename": "1848.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 45, "name": "Find", "long_name": "Find( int i , string k)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 91, "parameters": ["i", "k"], "filename": "1848.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 127, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "1848.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 40, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "1848.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1849.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43256110", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1849.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "185.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 275, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44881318", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 242, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "185.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1850.cpp", "nloc": 91, "token_count": 492, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43237623", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 72, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( long long x , long long y , long long MOD)", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x", "y", "MOD"], "filename": "1850.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 84, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( long long a , long long b , long long MOD)", "start_line": 50, "end_line": 64, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "1850.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 35, "name": "ispow2", "long_name": "ispow2( ll n)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 100, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1850.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 77, "name": "prime", "long_name": "prime( int x)", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1850.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "1850.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1851.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 394, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43086400", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 379, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 54, "parameters": [], "filename": "1851.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 50, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1852.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 394, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43086395", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 379, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1852.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1853.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43073689", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "2800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 238, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1853.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1854.cpp", "nloc": 11, "token_count": 99, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43045879", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "1854.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1855.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43025902", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1855.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1856.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43014211", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1856.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1857.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43009660", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1857.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1858.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43009472", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 309, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 84, "parameters": [], "filename": "1858.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 58, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1859.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43009242", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 23, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 262, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1859.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "186.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44833366", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "186.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1860.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 93, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43004097", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1860.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1861.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42972394", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1861.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1862.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42969870", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1862.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1863.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42959412", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1863.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1864.cpp", "nloc": 82, "token_count": 404, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42914559", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 33, "name": "Compare", "long_name": "Compare( const pair<int,int> & a , const pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1864.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 29, "name": "tostring", "long_name": "tostring( ll Number)", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["Number"], "filename": "1864.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 26, "name": "toint", "long_name": "toint( string String)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["String"], "filename": "1864.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 272, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 247, "parameters": [], "filename": "1864.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1865.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 264, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42913698", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 257, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1865.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1866.cpp", "nloc": 74, "token_count": 683, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42904738", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "precompute", "long_name": "precompute()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1866.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 65, "name": "fastMul", "long_name": "fastMul( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1866.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 65, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y , ll mod2)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y", "mod2"], "filename": "1866.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll x , ll mod)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x", "mod"], "filename": "1866.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 189, "name": "calcZ", "long_name": "calcZ( string s)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1866.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 199, "parameters": [], "filename": "1866.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1867.cpp", "nloc": 61, "token_count": 321, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42899861", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 249, "name": "solve1", "long_name": "solve1()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1867.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 61, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1867.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1868.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 264, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42895065", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 257, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1868.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 113, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1869.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42894139", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1869.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "187.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 300, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44830079", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 285, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "187.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1870.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 105, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42891654", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 98, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1870.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1871.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 128, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42880101", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1871.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1872.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 297, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42865997", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 290, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1872.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1873.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 310, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42863311", "exec_time": "1591 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 229, "parameters": [], "filename": "1873.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1874.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42857330", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1874.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1874.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1875.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 119, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42843630", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1875.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1876.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42828838", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1876.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1877.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42828551", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 25, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 254, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1877.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1878.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42827079", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 230, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1878.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1879.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42809402", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1879.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "188.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44830044", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "188.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1880.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 277, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42799768", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 272, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1880.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1881.cpp", "nloc": 11, "token_count": 92, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42791430", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1881.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1882.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42766066", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1882.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1883.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42752548", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 6, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "1883.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1884.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42749239", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 251, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "1884.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1885.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42742832", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 22, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 324, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1885.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 54, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1886.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42742036", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 250, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1886.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1887.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42739416", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 230, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "1887.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1888.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42739231", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 9, "parameters": [], "filename": "1888.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "readLL", "long_name": "readLL()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 10, "parameters": [], "filename": "1888.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "1888.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1889.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 225, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42738917", "exec_time": "1092 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1889.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 40, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "189.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44828620", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "189.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1890.cpp", "nloc": 78, "token_count": 439, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42738572", "exec_time": "1107 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 154, "name": "sieve", "long_name": "sieve()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 62, "parameters": [], "filename": "1890.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 64, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1890.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 48, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1891.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 265, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42738324", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 55, "token_count": 258, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1891.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1892.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 304, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42737785", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 54, "token_count": 291, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 100, "parameters": [], "filename": "1892.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 60, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1893.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 302, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42737270", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 21, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 297, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1893.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 50, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1894.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 270, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42736953", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 263, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "1894.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1895.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 463, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42728212", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 28, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 452, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1895.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1896.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42727506", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1896.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1897.cpp", "nloc": 10, "token_count": 91, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42725444", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "1897.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1898.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42716322", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 286, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1898.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1899.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42691885", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 77, "name": "find_substring", "long_name": "find_substring( string str , int start , string substring)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["str", "start", "substring"], "filename": "1899.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1899.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "19.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45490923", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "19.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "190.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 480, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44827563", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 435, "name": "compute", "long_name": "compute()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1900.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 258, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42673623", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1900.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1901.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42652606", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1901.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1902.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42602918", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 243, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1902.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1903.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42600295", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1903.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1904.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42592187", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1904.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1905.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 428, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42544840", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 51, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( const string & s , char c)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "1905.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "1905.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 61, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "1905.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1905.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1906.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42498147", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1906.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1907.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 326, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42477157", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 54, "token_count": 305, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1907.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1908.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42456030", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1908.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1909.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 334, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42451831", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 26, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 239, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 60, "parameters": [], "filename": "1909.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "191.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 246, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44818480", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 58, "parameters": [], "filename": "191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 52, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1910.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 349, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45699055", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "2100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 21, "name": "comp", "long_name": "comp( fff d , fff d1)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["d", "d1"], "filename": "1910.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 21, "name": "comp1", "long_name": "comp1( fff d , fff d1)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["d", "d1"], "filename": "1910.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 255, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1910.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1911.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45698478", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1911.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1912.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45621859", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "5500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 40, "name": "kor", "long_name": "kor( ll x)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1912.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "step", "long_name": "step( ll b , ui p)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["b", "p"], "filename": "1912.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 19, "name": "mdl", "long_name": "mdl( ll a)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1912.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1912.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1913.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45581060", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1913.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1914.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45577488", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1914.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1915.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45577199", "exec_time": "780 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 39, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const ii & p)", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["os", "p"], "filename": "1915.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 61, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int N , int M)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["N", "M"], "filename": "1915.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 65, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1915.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1916.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45570206", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 16, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1916.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1917.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45553953", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 241, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1917.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1918.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45466498", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "6800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 38, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( string s)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1918.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 43, "name": "isvowel", "long_name": "isvowel( char c)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "1918.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 49, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( pair<int,int> & a , pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1918.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 140, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1918.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 34, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "1918.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1919.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45466414", "exec_time": "389 ms", "memory": "6800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 38, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( string s)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1919.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 43, "name": "isvowel", "long_name": "isvowel( char c)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "1919.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 49, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( pair<int,int> & a , pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1919.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 140, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1919.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 34, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "1919.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "192.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44812315", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 171, "name": "MAIN", "long_name": "MAIN()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 46, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1920.cpp", "nloc": 2, "token_count": 117, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45446973", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "3600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 2, "end_line": 2, "parameters": [], "filename": "1920.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1923.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45440136", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1923.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1924.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45437214", "exec_time": "546 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1924.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1926.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45433864", "exec_time": "390 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 283, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1926.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1927.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45433081", "exec_time": "546 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1927.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1928.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45427463", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "3500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1928.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1929.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45422230", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1929.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "193.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44806136", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1930.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45419371", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "1700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1930.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1931.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45400915", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1931.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1932.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 280, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45344295", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "2200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1932.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1933.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45320661", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1933.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1934.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45314853", "exec_time": "483 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1934.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1935.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45305083", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1935.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1936.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45303537", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1936.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1937.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45284943", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1937.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1938.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45275866", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 81, "name": "cal", "long_name": "cal( int n)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1938.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 31, "name": "cal2", "long_name": "cal2( map<int,int> & mp , int n)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["mp", "n"], "filename": "1938.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1938.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1939.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45250290", "exec_time": "373 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1939.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "194.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 261, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44803998", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 254, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "194.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1940.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 288, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45228805", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "8600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1940.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "boost", "long_name": "boost()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1940.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "1940.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1941.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 415, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45216025", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "7900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 84, "name": "divi", "long_name": "divi( int x)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1941.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "1941.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1942.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45211141", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int x , int y)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1942.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 29, "name": "lif", "long_name": "lif( float x)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1942.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "1942.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1943.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 286, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45199302", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1943.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1944.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 283, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45189079", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "snum", "long_name": "snum( ll & a)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1944.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "snum", "long_name": "snum( ll & a , ll & b)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1944.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "snum", "long_name": "snum( ll & a , ll & b , ll & c)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1944.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 37, "name": "snum", "long_name": "snum( ll & a , ll & b , ll & c , ll & d)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "filename": "1944.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1944.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1945.cpp", "nloc": 110, "token_count": 2418, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45171774", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 38, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( t & a)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 43, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( pair<t,t1> & p)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 53, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( vector<t> & V)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["V"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 53, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( deque<t> & D)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["D"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( vector<t> & V , ll dim)", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["V", "dim"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( deque<t> & D , ll dim)", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["D", "dim"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( set<t> & S , ll dim)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["S", "dim"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( multiset<t> & M , ll dim)", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["M", "dim"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 52, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( priority_queue<t,vector<t>> & P , ll dim)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["P", "dim"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( priority_queue<t,vector<t>,greater<t>> & P , ll dim)", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["P", "dim"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( t a)", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( pair<t,t1> p)", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( vector<t> & V)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 157, "parameters": ["V"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( deque<t> & D)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["D"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( set<t> & S)", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 161, "parameters": ["S"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( multiset<t> & M)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 163, "parameters": ["M"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 91, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( priority_queue<t,vector<t>> & P)", "start_line": 165, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["P"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 96, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( priority_queue<t,vector<t>,greater<t>> & P)", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 167, "parameters": ["P"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( const Arg & arg , const Args & ... args)", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["arg", "args"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( Arg & arg , Args & ... args)", "start_line": 177, "end_line": 177, "parameters": ["arg", "args"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "GCD", "long_name": "GCD( t a , t b)", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 191, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "LCM", "long_name": "LCM( t a , t b)", "start_line": 193, "end_line": 193, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "abs", "long_name": "abs( t a , t b)", "start_line": 195, "end_line": 195, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "abs", "long_name": "abs( t a)", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 197, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int a , int b)", "start_line": 199, "end_line": 199, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( double a , double b)", "start_line": 201, "end_line": 201, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ld a , ld b)", "start_line": 203, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 205, "end_line": 205, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( int a , int b)", "start_line": 207, "end_line": 207, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( double a , double b)", "start_line": 209, "end_line": 209, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ld a , ld b)", "start_line": 211, "end_line": 211, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 213, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "StringToVector", "long_name": "StringToVector( string s)", "start_line": 215, "end_line": 215, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "StringToVectorInt", "long_name": "StringToVectorInt( string s)", "start_line": 217, "end_line": 217, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "NumberToString", "long_name": "NumberToString( t number)", "start_line": 219, "end_line": 219, "parameters": ["number"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "StringToNumber", "long_name": "StringToNumber( string s)", "start_line": 221, "end_line": 221, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "StringToNumberInt", "long_name": "StringToNumberInt( string s)", "start_line": 223, "end_line": 223, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 235, "end_line": 265, "parameters": [], "filename": "1945.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1946.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45168775", "exec_time": "546 ms", "memory": "12700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1946.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1947.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 286, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45146757", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 271, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1947.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1948.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45134409", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "3500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1948.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1949.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45133697", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1949.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "195.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44797452", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "195.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1950.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45108178", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "8800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 12, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1950.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1951.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45108120", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "6400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 12, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1951.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1952.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45108097", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "6400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 12, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1952.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1953.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45108051", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "7500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1953.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1954.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45103452", "exec_time": "577 ms", "memory": "4600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1954.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1955.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45094321", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1955.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 42, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1956.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45090226", "exec_time": "577 ms", "memory": "8800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1956.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1957.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45076640", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "5300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1957.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1958.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45074685", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1958.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1959.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45074083", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1959.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "196.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44790083", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "196.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1960.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45071151", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 214, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1960.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1961.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45069847", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "2200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 27, "used_macros": 27, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1961.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1962.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 268, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45068791", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "5100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1962.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 115, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1962.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1963.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 166, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45067583", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1963.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1964.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45067224", "exec_time": "529 ms", "memory": "5800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1964.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1965.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/45038186", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1965.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1966.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 442, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44981559", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 80, "name": "modexpo", "long_name": "modexpo( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1966.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "intpoint", "long_name": "intpoint( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "1966.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "isvalid", "long_name": "isvalid( ll x , ll y , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x", "y", "n", "m"], "filename": "1966.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1966.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1967.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 371, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44979974", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "5300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1967.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 30, "name": "update", "long_name": "update( int idx)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["idx"], "filename": "1967.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "query", "long_name": "query( int idx)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["idx"], "filename": "1967.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 258, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1967.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1968.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44979565", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "15100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1968.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1969.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 128, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44967990", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "3500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1969.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "197.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 331, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44779984", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 164, "name": "cntmax", "long_name": "cntmax( int * arr1 , int * arr2 , int i , int j , int n , int m)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["arr1", "arr2", "i", "j", "n", "m"], "filename": "197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 42, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1970.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 272, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44938184", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1970.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1971.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44928969", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1971.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1972.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44915541", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "8800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "1972.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1973.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 391, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44914437", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "8200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "fastpow", "long_name": "fastpow( ll n , ll x)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "1973.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 56, "name": "fastpowDouble", "long_name": "fastpowDouble( double n , ll x)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "1973.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "my_mod", "long_name": "my_mod( ll num , ll mod)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["num", "mod"], "filename": "1973.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1973.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 191, "parameters": [], "filename": "1973.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1974.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44911216", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1974.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1974.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "1974.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1975.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 1821, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44909791", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 25, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 56, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 83, "name": "isPrime", "long_name": "isPrime( T n)", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 191, "name": "sieve", "long_name": "sieve( T N)", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["N"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 107, "name": "factorization", "long_name": "factorization( T N)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 157, "parameters": ["N"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( T a , T b)", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 161, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 62, "name": "mmul", "long_name": "mmul( T a , T b , T m)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 163, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 64, "name": "bigMod", "long_name": "bigMod( T a , T b , T m)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 163, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "negMod", "long_name": "negMod( T n , T m)", "start_line": 165, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["n", "m"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 78, "name": "bigMul", "long_name": "bigMul( T a , T b , T m)", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 167, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "StoI", "long_name": "StoI( string s , T ret)", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 169, "parameters": ["s", "ret"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "ItoS", "long_name": "ItoS( T n)", "start_line": 171, "end_line": 171, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 55, "name": "MIN3", "long_name": "MIN3( T x , T y , T z)", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["x", "y", "z"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 55, "name": "MAX3", "long_name": "MAX3( T x , T y , T z)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 175, "parameters": ["x", "y", "z"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "BtoD", "long_name": "BtoD( T x)", "start_line": 177, "end_line": 177, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 66, "name": "BtoD", "long_name": "BtoD( string str)", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 179, "parameters": ["str"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 73, "name": "DtoB", "long_name": "DtoB( ULL n)", "start_line": 181, "end_line": 181, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 119, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( T & x)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 185, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "in2", "long_name": "in2( T & a , T & b)", "start_line": 187, "end_line": 187, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "in3", "long_name": "in3( T & a , T & b , T & c)", "start_line": 189, "end_line": 189, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 97, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( T x)", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 191, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "Rem", "long_name": "Rem( string q , LL r)", "start_line": 193, "end_line": 193, "parameters": ["q", "r"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 106, "name": "quotient", "long_name": "quotient( string num , LL number)", "start_line": 195, "end_line": 195, "parameters": ["num", "number"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 40, "name": "isVowel", "long_name": "isVowel( char ch)", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 197, "parameters": ["ch"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "isConsonant", "long_name": "isConsonant( char ch)", "start_line": 199, "end_line": 199, "parameters": ["ch"], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 259, "parameters": [], "filename": "1975.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1976.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 119, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44898235", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "7200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 95, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1976.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1977.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 353, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44853500", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 34, "used_macros": 34, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( int a , int b , int p = mod)", "start_line": 54, "end_line": 54, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1977.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "sub", "long_name": "sub( int a , int b , int p = mod)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1977.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( int a , int b , int p = mod)", "start_line": 56, "end_line": 56, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1977.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1977.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1978.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44838585", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "14800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "umin", "long_name": "umin( T & a , T b)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1978.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "umax", "long_name": "umax( T & a , T b)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1978.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 104, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1978.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 5, "name": "preprocess", "long_name": "preprocess()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1978.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 25, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "1978.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1979.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44820482", "exec_time": "373 ms", "memory": "9400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1979.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "198.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44779733", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "198.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1980.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44751998", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 24, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 252, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1980.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1981.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44680152", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1981.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1982.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44657672", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1982.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1983.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44621308", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1983.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1984.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44614495", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1984.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1985.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44586374", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "4600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 35, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1985.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1986.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44564073", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1986.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1987.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44556301", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1987.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1988.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 542, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44530136", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 27, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "on_bit", "long_name": "on_bit( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "off_bit", "long_name": "off_bit( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "is_on_bit", "long_name": "is_on_bit( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "flip_bit", "long_name": "flip_bit( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "lsb", "long_name": "lsb( int x)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "on_bit_all", "long_name": "on_bit_all( int x , int pos)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["x", "pos"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 125, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "sub", "long_name": "sub( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 58, "name": "inid", "long_name": "inid()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 81, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 193, "parameters": [], "filename": "1988.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1989.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44520070", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1989.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "199.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44778186", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "199.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1990.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44490397", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1990.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1991.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44480962", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1991.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1992.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44473032", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1992.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1993.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44445517", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1993.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1994.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 310, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44436511", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 275, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "1994.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 95, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1995.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 315, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44436330", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 280, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "1995.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1996.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44423819", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1996.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1997.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44400616", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1997.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1998.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44400377", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1998.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1999.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44399564", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1999.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45694633", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "2100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "20.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45472608", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "20.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "200.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44774180", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2000.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 434, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44377842", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 49, "name": "sortpair", "long_name": "sortpair( const pair<int,int> & x , const pair<int,int> & y)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "dcomp", "long_name": "dcomp( double x , double y)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "smile", "long_name": "smile()", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "2000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 36, "name": "printarr", "long_name": "printarr( int arr [ ] , int n)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["]", "n"], "filename": "2000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 59, "name": "printset", "long_name": "printset( int n)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 205, "parameters": [], "filename": "2000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2001.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44376017", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "2001.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2002.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44342801", "exec_time": "560 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2002.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2003.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 246, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44341500", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2003.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2004.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44340045", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2004.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2005.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44334771", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2005.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2006.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 305, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44229813", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "2006.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2007.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44222052", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2007.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2008.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 345, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44185997", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 25, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 63, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "2008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "descending", "long_name": "descending( int a , int b)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "2008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2009.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44183803", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2009.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "201.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44762621", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2010.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44178819", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "3500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2011.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 236, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44110632", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "47200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2012.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44095944", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2012.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2013.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44088624", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2013.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2014.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44088579", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "8200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2014.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2015.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44070168", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "4400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 247, "end_line": 283, "parameters": [], "filename": "2015.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2016.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44066419", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2016.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2017.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44058980", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2017.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2018.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44042458", "exec_time": "623 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2018.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2019.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44040280", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 12, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2019.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "202.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44759607", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2020.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44040251", "exec_time": "670 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2021.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44028408", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2021.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2022.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44022584", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2023.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/44007374", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2023.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2024.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43981847", "exec_time": "655 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2024.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2025.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43979893", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 146, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2025.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2025.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2026.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43979870", "exec_time": "264 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 125, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2026.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 46, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2026.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2027.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43975766", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2027.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2028.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43971385", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2028.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2029.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 260, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43930118", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 34, "name": "update", "long_name": "update( int idx , int mx)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["idx", "mx"], "filename": "2029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 39, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( int idx)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["idx"], "filename": "2029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "203.cpp", "nloc": 112, "token_count": 825, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44757441", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 9, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 35, "name": "Edge::Edge", "long_name": "Edge::Edge( int t , int c , bool real = true)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["t", "c", "true"], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 11, "name": "Edge::residual", "long_name": "Edge::residual() const", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 23, "name": "Graph::Graph", "long_name": "Graph::Graph( int n)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 32, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 10, "name": "Graph::~Graph", "long_name": "Graph::~Graph()", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 85, "name": "Graph::add_edge", "long_name": "Graph::add_edge( int u , int v , int cap)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["u", "v", "cap"], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 104, "name": "push_path", "long_name": "push_path( Graph & G , int s , int t , const vector<EdgeIter> & path , int flow)", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 64, "parameters": ["G", "s", "t", "path", "flow"], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 179, "name": "augmenting_path", "long_name": "augmenting_path( const Graph & G , int s , int t , vector<EdgeIter> & path , vector<bool> & visited , int step = 0)", "start_line": 68, "end_line": 88, "parameters": ["G", "s", "t", "path", "visited", "0"], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 113, "name": "network_flow", "long_name": "network_flow( Graph & G , int s , int t)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 106, "parameters": ["G", "s", "t"], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 112, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2030.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43929743", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 19, "name": "way", "long_name": "way( query q1 , query q2)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["q1", "q2"], "filename": "2030.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "2030.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2031.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43918209", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "5100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2031.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2032.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43912914", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2032.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2033.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43905674", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "3500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 217, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2033.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2034.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43905025", "exec_time": "624 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2034.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2035.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43875275", "exec_time": "638 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( int a , int b)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2035.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2035.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2036.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43831936", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2037.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43803900", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "12000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2037.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2038.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43802349", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2038.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2039.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 132, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43754373", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "204.cpp", "nloc": 68, "token_count": 646, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44752174", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 154, "name": "MaxMatching::max_matching", "long_name": "MaxMatching::max_matching( const vector<vi> & g)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 28, "parameters": ["g"], "filename": "204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 157, "name": "MaxMatching::bfs", "long_name": "MaxMatching::bfs( const vector<vi> & g , vi & used , vi & A , vi & D)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 42, "parameters": ["g", "used", "A", "D"], "filename": "204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 121, "name": "MaxMatching::dfs", "long_name": "MaxMatching::dfs( const vector<vi> & g , vi & vis , vi & used , vi & match , vi & D , int u)", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 58, "parameters": ["g", "vis", "used", "match", "D", "u"], "filename": "204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 161, "parameters": [], "filename": "204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2040.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 349, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43742056", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "5400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 36, "used_macros": 36, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "abs", "long_name": "abs( T x)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2040.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "mini", "long_name": "mini( T x , T y)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2040.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "maxi", "long_name": "maxi( T x , T y)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2040.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2040.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 183, "parameters": [], "filename": "2040.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2041.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43724248", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2041.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2042.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43717666", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2042.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2043.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43694554", "exec_time": "607 ms", "memory": "1700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2043.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2044.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43676176", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2044.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2045.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43675731", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 214, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2045.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2046.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43671152", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "2046.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2047.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43667385", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2047.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2048.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 145, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43650068", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "5100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2048.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2049.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43648255", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "5700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2049.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "205.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44750858", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 33, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( const vector<ll> & a , const vector<ll> & b)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "205.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "205.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2050.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43635610", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2050.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2051.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43633477", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2052.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43628893", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2052.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2053.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43623017", "exec_time": "624 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2053.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2054.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43605697", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2054.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2055.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43591415", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2055.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2056.cpp", "nloc": 74, "token_count": 394, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43586322", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 31, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 27, "name": "MOD", "long_name": "MOD( int a , int b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "max3", "long_name": "max3( ll a , ll b , ll c)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "2056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 68, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 42, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 211, "parameters": [], "filename": "2056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2057.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43585997", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2057.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2058.cpp", "nloc": 72, "token_count": 523, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43581926", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "2058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "modInv", "long_name": "modInv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "2058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "2058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "mpower", "long_name": "mpower( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 51, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 90, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2059.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43580909", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 8, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 32, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "2059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "206.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44746967", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2060.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43573878", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 19, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "2060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2061.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43567727", "exec_time": "529 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2061.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2062.cpp", "nloc": 84, "token_count": 447, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43555275", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "5500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 85, "name": "isPrime", "long_name": "isPrime( ll n)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 77, "name": "seive", "long_name": "seive()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "2062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 157, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 215, "parameters": [], "filename": "2062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 219, "end_line": 263, "parameters": [], "filename": "2062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2063.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 385, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43524423", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 33, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "2063.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2064.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43521787", "exec_time": "546 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "2064.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2065.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43521108", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 157, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2065.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2066.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43520410", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2066.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2067.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43516475", "exec_time": "373 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 110, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "2067.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2068.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43495844", "exec_time": "639 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2068.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2069.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43470747", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "207.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44746443", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 111, "name": "matchpair", "long_name": "matchpair( int * barr , int * garr , int m , int n)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["barr", "garr", "m", "n"], "filename": "207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2070.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 496, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43468000", "exec_time": "467 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , pair<S,T> const & p)", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "2070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 73, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , vector<T> const & v)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 28, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "2070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * name , T && arg1)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 62, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * names , T && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 223, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "2070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 40, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2071.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43460651", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "8800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2072.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43457230", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2073.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43434686", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2074.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43430632", "exec_time": "390 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "2074.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2075.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43430268", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2075.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2076.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43428016", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2076.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2077.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43428014", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2078.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43427955", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 20, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2078.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2079.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43427818", "exec_time": "483 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2079.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "208.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44745791", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 214, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2080.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43425113", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2080.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2081.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43418523", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2081.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2082.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43418161", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2082.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2083.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43418060", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 20, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "2083.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2084.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43417986", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2084.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2085.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43417821", "exec_time": "654 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "2085.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2086.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43417785", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2087.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43417774", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "2087.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2088.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43417762", "exec_time": "186 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "2088.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2089.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43417700", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 21, "used_headers": 19, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 25, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 195, "parameters": [], "filename": "2089.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "209.cpp", "nloc": 87, "token_count": 729, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44745678", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 179, "name": "MaxMatching::max_matching", "long_name": "MaxMatching::max_matching( const vector<vector<int>> & graph)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["graph"], "filename": "209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 197, "name": "MaxMatching::bfs", "long_name": "MaxMatching::bfs( const vector<vector<int>> & graph , vector<bool> & used , vector<int> & mapping , vector<int> & dist)", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 56, "parameters": ["graph", "used", "mapping", "dist"], "filename": "209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 134, "name": "MaxMatching::dfs", "long_name": "MaxMatching::dfs( const vector<vector<int>> & graph , vector<bool> & vis , vector<bool> & used , vector<int> & matching , vector<int> & dist , int u1)", "start_line": 58, "end_line": 72, "parameters": ["graph", "vis", "used", "matching", "dist", "u1"], "filename": "209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 108, "parameters": [], "filename": "209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2090.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 275, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43417647", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "10800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 23, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 54, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "2090.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2091.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43417551", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "3400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2091.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2092.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43415847", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2092.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2093.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43413834", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2093.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2094.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43395426", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2095.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43372910", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2096.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43292378", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "5700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2097.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43266665", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2097.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2098.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 597, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43233107", "exec_time": "577 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "fpow", "long_name": "fpow( ll n , ll k , ll p = MOD)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["n", "k", "MOD"], "filename": "2098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll a , ll p = MOD)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["a", "MOD"], "filename": "2098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 91, "name": "Sqrt", "long_name": "Sqrt( ll x)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 69, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 83, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( ll & no)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["no"], "filename": "2098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "2098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2099.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43176871", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 0, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2099.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "21.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45468750", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "21.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "210.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 536, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44739137", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 529, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2100.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43176288", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 25, "name": "swap", "long_name": "swap( ll & a , ll & b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 72, "parameters": [], "filename": "2100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2101.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 246, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43155194", "exec_time": "546 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 172, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 44, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2102.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43089773", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2102.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2103.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43071847", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2104.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 649, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43065710", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 32, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "dcmp", "long_name": "dcmp( ld d1 , ld d2)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["d1", "d2"], "filename": "2104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 25, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "ord", "long_name": "ord( int r , int c , int nCol)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["r", "c", "nCol"], "filename": "2104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 46, "name": "rord", "long_name": "rord( int n , int nCol)", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["n", "nCol"], "filename": "2104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 65, "name": "poww", "long_name": "poww( ll num , ll p , ll md)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 151, "parameters": ["num", "p", "md"], "filename": "2104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 44, "name": "nCr", "long_name": "nCr( ll n , ll r)", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 167, "parameters": ["n", "r"], "filename": "2104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 203, "parameters": [], "filename": "2104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2105.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43065291", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2106.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43045685", "exec_time": "560 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2107.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43019570", "exec_time": "577 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2108.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43018899", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 44, "name": "get", "long_name": "get( int l)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["l"], "filename": "2108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 73, "name": "initFenwick", "long_name": "initFenwick()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "2108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2109.cpp", "nloc": 61, "token_count": 553, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43011224", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 52, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 65, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 78, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 183, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 187, "end_line": 209, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "modinv", "long_name": "modinv( ll a , ll p)", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 219, "parameters": ["a", "p"], "filename": "2109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 229, "end_line": 255, "parameters": [], "filename": "2109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "211.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44735051", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2110.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43009264", "exec_time": "326 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2111.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/43008727", "exec_time": "623 ms", "memory": "2900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2112.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42937677", "exec_time": "577 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 27, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact( long long x)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2113.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42915441", "exec_time": "623 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2114.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 291, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42913749", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 72, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( LL x , LL y , LL p = 1e18 + 10)", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["x", "y", "10"], "filename": "2114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2115.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42904404", "exec_time": "389 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 31, "used_macros": 30, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "sbt", "long_name": "sbt( int x)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "2115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2116.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42899922", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2117.cpp", "nloc": 108, "token_count": 705, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42899082", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "5900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 74, "name": "bigmod", "long_name": "bigmod( long long p , long long e , long long M)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 91, "parameters": ["p", "e", "M"], "filename": "2117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "modinverse", "long_name": "modinverse( ll a , ll M)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["a", "M"], "filename": "2117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 66, "name": "bigmod", "long_name": "bigmod( ll base , ll pow)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["base", "pow"], "filename": "2117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 104, "name": "sieve", "long_name": "sieve()", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "2117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 77, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs( int lo , int hi , int k)", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["lo", "hi", "k"], "filename": "2117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 229, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 205, "end_line": 289, "parameters": [], "filename": "2117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2118.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42896633", "exec_time": "608 ms", "memory": "6800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2119.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42896456", "exec_time": "608 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2119.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "212.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44721332", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2120.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42860674", "exec_time": "389 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2121.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42860084", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 13, "parameters": [], "filename": "2121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2122.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42859422", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 38, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 177, "parameters": [], "filename": "2122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2123.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42858167", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2124.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42850726", "exec_time": "654 ms", "memory": "22100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "2124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2125.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42810592", "exec_time": "326 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 238, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2126.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42798333", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2127.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42785874", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2128.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42785545", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2129.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42755332", "exec_time": "639 ms", "memory": "5300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2129.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "213.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44703214", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2130.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42752739", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2131.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42750288", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2132.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42749881", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "Doaa", "long_name": "Doaa()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "2132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2133.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42747126", "exec_time": "624 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2134.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42733306", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2134.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2135.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42711715", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2136.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42709475", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2137.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42709373", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 85, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int a [ ] , int n)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["]", "n"], "filename": "2137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2138.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42701953", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "printprecise", "long_name": "printprecise( double l , ll precision)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["l", "precision"], "filename": "2138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "2138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2139.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42695328", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2139.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "214.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44702846", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2140.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42682318", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2141.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42647557", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "2141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2142.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42629134", "exec_time": "264 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2143.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 255, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42590429", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2144.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 411, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42551690", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 51, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( const string & s , char c)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "2144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "2144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 61, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "2144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2145.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42546360", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2145.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2146.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42500237", "exec_time": "624 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2146.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2147.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42496792", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2147.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2148.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 404, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42478346", "exec_time": "326 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "2148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2149.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 236, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42477452", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "215.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44697587", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2150.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 380, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42454059", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 76, "name": "Read", "long_name": "Read( int & n)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 76, "name": "Read", "long_name": "Read( ll & n)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2151.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42409341", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "2151.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2152.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42359790", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "fastio", "long_name": "fastio()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 15, "parameters": [], "filename": "2152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2153.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 361, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42336515", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 83, "name": "xxx::rd", "long_name": "xxx::rd()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 57, "name": "xxx::pow_mod", "long_name": "xxx::pow_mod( ll a , ll n)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["a", "n"], "filename": "2153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 101, "name": "MAIN", "long_name": "MAIN()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "2153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2157.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 354, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42308007", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "arin", "long_name": "arin( T * st , T * nd)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["st", "nd"], "filename": "2157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "cmd", "long_name": "cmd( pair<pair<int,int>,int> a , pair<pair<int,int>,int> b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2158.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 354, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42307981", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "arin", "long_name": "arin( T * st , T * nd)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["st", "nd"], "filename": "2158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "cmd", "long_name": "cmd( pair<pair<int,int>,int> a , pair<pair<int,int>,int> b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2159.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42273193", "exec_time": "467 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "216.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44693978", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2160.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42228471", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2161.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 145, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42222590", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "2700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2161.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2162.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 166, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42222493", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2162.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2163.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42222432", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2163.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2164.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42222215", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2164.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2165.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42222047", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2165.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2166.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42218875", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2167.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42211040", "exec_time": "608 ms", "memory": "11700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2167.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2168.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42120788", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2169.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42120643", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "217.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44681451", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "217.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2170.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42070620", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2171.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42062663", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int , char **)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["int", "**"], "filename": "2171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2172.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 422, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/42007223", "exec_time": "390 ms", "memory": "13300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 32, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 86, "name": "seive", "long_name": "seive()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "2172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 84, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs( ll a [ ] , ll x , ll n)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["]", "x", "n"], "filename": "2172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 219, "parameters": [], "filename": "2172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2173.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 118, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41943187", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2173.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2174.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41936690", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "2174.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2175.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41927347", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2175.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2176.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41913163", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 39, "name": "count", "long_name": "count( ll n)", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 10, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2176.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "2176.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2177.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41899312", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2177.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2178.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41897818", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2178.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2179.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41894347", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "11100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "218.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44681347", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "218.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 121, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2180.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41820044", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "5900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 217, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2180.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2181.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41819960", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 105, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 41, "name": "print", "long_name": "print()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 13, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2182.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41816536", "exec_time": "529 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2182.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2183.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41728425", "exec_time": "639 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2184.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41685356", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2184.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2185.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41682617", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2185.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2186.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41678809", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "11100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2186.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2187.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 349, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41678539", "exec_time": "264 ms", "memory": "19000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "2187.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2188.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41678249", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2188.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2189.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 225, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41678164", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2189.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "219.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44681218", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "219.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2190.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41663773", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2191.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41653761", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "11100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "2191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2192.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 515, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41651655", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 97, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( Drake & x)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 47, "name": "write", "long_name": "write( Drake x)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( Drake x)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 76, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 21, "name": "cmpnum", "long_name": "cmpnum( data cmp1 , data cmp2)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["cmp1", "cmp2"], "filename": "2192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 21, "name": "cmpi", "long_name": "cmpi( data cmp1 , data cmp2)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["cmp1", "cmp2"], "filename": "2192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 161, "parameters": [], "filename": "2192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2193.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 491, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41647910", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 86, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "2193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 103, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read( mitsuha & x)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "chtholly::write", "long_name": "chtholly::write( mitsuha x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "chtholly::fuhao", "long_name": "chtholly::fuhao()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2194.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 130, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41633508", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2194.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2195.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41630875", "exec_time": "483 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2195.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2196.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41622106", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2196.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2197.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41618975", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "4600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "2197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 119, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2198.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41540088", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "2198.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2199.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41506581", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "8000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2199.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "22.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45454580", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "22.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "220.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44681080", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "220.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2200.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41435537", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 56, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2201.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41409717", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2202.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41401770", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 215, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "2202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2203.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41381338", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 41, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( double x , double y = 0 , double tol = EPS)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["x", "0", "EPS"], "filename": "2203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "2203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2204.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41298269", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2205.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41294833", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2205.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2206.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41278623", "exec_time": "311 ms", "memory": "15500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 57, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "2206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 91, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 13, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2207.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41272416", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2208.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41248559", "exec_time": "264 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2209.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41229386", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "221.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44674728", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 230, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2210.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41226398", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "7000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2211.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41127089", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "2900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 208, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char ** argv)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["argc", "argv"], "filename": "2211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2212.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41112530", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2213.cpp", "nloc": 127, "token_count": 988, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/41085741", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "19000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 14, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 27, "used_macros": 27, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "INPUT", "long_name": "INPUT( int * a , int size)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["a", "size"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "OUTPUT", "long_name": "OUTPUT( int * a , int size)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a", "size"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( T1 a , T2 b)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( T1 a , T2 b)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 43, "name": "POW", "long_name": "POW( int a , int n)", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["a", "n"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 26, "name": "to_string", "long_name": "to_string( int n)", "start_line": 165, "end_line": 179, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 42, "name": "to_binary", "long_name": "to_binary( int n)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 76, "name": "GCD_E", "long_name": "GCD_E( int a , int b , int & x , int & y)", "start_line": 209, "end_line": 233, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "addMOD", "long_name": "addMOD( int a , int b , int m = MOD)", "start_line": 239, "end_line": 245, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "mulMOD", "long_name": "mulMOD( int a , int b , int m = MOD)", "start_line": 251, "end_line": 257, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 56, "name": "divMOD", "long_name": "divMOD( int a , int b , int m = MOD)", "start_line": 263, "end_line": 275, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 34, "name": "C", "long_name": "C( int k , int n)", "start_line": 281, "end_line": 287, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 88, "name": "solution", "long_name": "solution()", "start_line": 319, "end_line": 349, "parameters": [], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 39, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 353, "end_line": 375, "parameters": [], "filename": "2213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2214.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40924457", "exec_time": "670 ms", "memory": "10200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 13, "name": "lowbit", "long_name": "lowbit( int x)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 37, "name": "sum", "long_name": "sum( int cur)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["cur"], "filename": "2214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 34, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( int cur , int x)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["cur", "x"], "filename": "2214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "2214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2215.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 325, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40872394", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 35, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int i , int j , int n , int m)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["i", "j", "n", "m"], "filename": "2215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "func", "long_name": "func( pair<int,int> & a , pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 53, "name": "tol", "long_name": "tol( string & a)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2216.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40811928", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "5700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "prn", "long_name": "prn( T first)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["first"], "filename": "2216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 25, "name": "prn", "long_name": "prn( T first , Args ... args)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["first", "args"], "filename": "2216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "2216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2217.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40771627", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2217.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2218.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40767656", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2218.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2219.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 314, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40767160", "exec_time": "467 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( data a , data b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2219.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "2219.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "222.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 308, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44671442", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 301, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2220.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40679030", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "2220.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2221.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40666687", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2222.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40623565", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "6500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2223.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 417, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40533111", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "tostr", "long_name": "tostr(string&s,auto num)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "toint", "long_name": "toint(auto&num,string s)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact(auto n)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod(auto a,auto b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm(auto a,auto b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2224.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40477338", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2225.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40468576", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2226.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 248, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40251807", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "9800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2227.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40245172", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2227.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2228.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40205537", "exec_time": "483 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "2228.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2229.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40201133", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2229.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "223.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 361, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44669072", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 33, "name": "belong_maxi", "long_name": "belong_maxi( int name)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["name"], "filename": "223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 270, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2230.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40193612", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2230.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2231.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40183902", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "2231.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2232.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 732, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/40086355", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "12700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 9, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "strtoll", "long_name": "strtoll( string s)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lltostr", "long_name": "lltostr( ll n)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 92, "name": "llsqrt", "long_name": "llsqrt( ll x)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 121, "name": "sieve", "long_name": "sieve( ll size)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["size"], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 76, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "modInverse", "long_name": "modInverse( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 83, "name": "fastscan", "long_name": "fastscan( ll & number)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["number"], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 189, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 183, "parameters": [], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 189, "end_line": 219, "parameters": [], "filename": "2232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2233.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39981362", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2233.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2234.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39973217", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2235.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39861309", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "4400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2236.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39853849", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 19, "name": "prep", "long_name": "prep()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "2236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2237.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 184, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39803478", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2237.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2238.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39792824", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2238.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2239.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39762422", "exec_time": "701 ms", "memory": "11300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "224.cpp", "nloc": 72, "token_count": 459, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44667335", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "factorize", "long_name": "factorize( int n)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 40, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 66, "name": "multiple", "long_name": "multiple( lli a , lli b , lli c)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 30, "name": "GCD", "long_name": "GCD( int A , int B)", "start_line": 68, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["A", "B"], "filename": "224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 25, "name": "Log2", "long_name": "Log2( li x)", "start_line": 96, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 23, "name": "mini", "long_name": "mini( lli a , lli b)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 108, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 23, "name": "maxe", "long_name": "maxe( lli a , lli b)", "start_line": 110, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 144, "parameters": [], "filename": "224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2240.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39762411", "exec_time": "639 ms", "memory": "11300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2240.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2241.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39758209", "exec_time": "545 ms", "memory": "5700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 62, "parameters": [], "filename": "2241.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2242.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39651599", "exec_time": "483 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2242.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2243.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39645002", "exec_time": "608 ms", "memory": "26100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2243.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2244.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 451, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39598321", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 12, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 51, "name": "DSU::DSU", "long_name": "DSU::DSU( int n)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "DSU::getRoot", "long_name": "DSU::getRoot( int ind)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["ind"], "filename": "2244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 21, "name": "DSU::connected", "long_name": "DSU::connected( int ind1 , int ind2)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["ind1", "ind2"], "filename": "2244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 88, "name": "DSU::connect", "long_name": "DSU::connect( int ind1 , int ind2)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["ind1", "ind2"], "filename": "2244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "DSU::showId", "long_name": "DSU::showId( int n)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 193, "parameters": [], "filename": "2244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2245.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39403216", "exec_time": "639 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2245.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2246.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39343852", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "49300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2246.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2247.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39260674", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2247.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2248.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 319, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39222788", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "7200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 78, "name": "SieveOfErat", "long_name": "SieveOfErat()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2248.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 32, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll aa , ll id2)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["aa", "id2"], "filename": "2248.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 171, "parameters": [], "filename": "2248.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2249.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39080590", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "225.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 298, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44660976", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 255, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2250.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 424, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39038780", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , pair<S,T> const & p)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "2250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 73, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , vector<T> const & v)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "2250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * name , T && arg1)", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 34, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 62, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * names , T && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2251.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39029581", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2251.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2252.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/39028940", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 203, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2253.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38983965", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2253.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2254.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38980623", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "2254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2255.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38923314", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2256.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 437, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38921738", "exec_time": "311 ms", "memory": "7200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "used_macros": 21, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( ll a , ll b , ll m = mod)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "2256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 42, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll a , ll b , ll m = mod)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "2256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 82, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b , ll m = mod)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "2256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2257.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 437, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38921706", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( ll a , ll b , ll m = mod)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "2257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 42, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll a , ll b , ll m = mod)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "2257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 82, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b , ll m = mod)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "2257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2258.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 383, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38828177", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "smin", "long_name": "smin( T & a , T val)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "val"], "filename": "2258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "smax", "long_name": "smax( T & a , T val)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["a", "val"], "filename": "2258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 66, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "2258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2259.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38680577", "exec_time": "623 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2259.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "226.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44660224", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2260.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38631745", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "5700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2260.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2261.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38615646", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2261.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2262.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38613554", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2263.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38600776", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2263.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2264.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38543050", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 15, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "lin", "long_name": "lin()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "2264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2265.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38542023", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "2265.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2266.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 388, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38537648", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "2266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2267.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 543, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38463267", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 7, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 66, "name": "mexp", "long_name": "mexp( ll x , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["x", "n", "m"], "filename": "2267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "ispow2", "long_name": "ispow2( ll x)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int x , int y)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 251, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "2267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2268.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38351981", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( int a , int b)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2269.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38263774", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2269.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "227.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44658262", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "227.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2270.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38250112", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2271.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38074112", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "7300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2272.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/38056264", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "6400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 22, "used_headers": 22, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "2272.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2273.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37926401", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "4400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2273.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2274.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37907675", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "2274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2275.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37880317", "exec_time": "624 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2275.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2276.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 381, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37874168", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 25, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 64, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "2276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2277.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37746107", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "2277.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2278.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37696403", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "RTC::~RTC", "long_name": "RTC::~RTC()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 11, "parameters": [], "filename": "2278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2279.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37688794", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2279.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "228.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44648632", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "228.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2280.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37643331", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "2280.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2281.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37583631", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "4600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2281.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2282.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37561311", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2282.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2283.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37548595", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "2283.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2284.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37541220", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "6300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2285.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37533643", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2285.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2286.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37509383", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "7500 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 14, "parameters": [], "filename": "2286.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2287.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37468457", "exec_time": "670 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "2287.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2288.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 344, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37369544", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 24, "name": "between", "long_name": "between( int x , int l , int r)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["x", "l", "r"], "filename": "2288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "tostring", "long_name": "tostring( int x)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 79, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( int & number)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["number"], "filename": "2288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 110, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "2288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2289.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37140358", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2289.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "229.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44612537", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 225, "parameters": [], "filename": "229.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2290.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37116954", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2290.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2292.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37017818", "exec_time": "264 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 24, "used_headers": 24, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "2292.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2293.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/37008362", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "6400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 8, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2293.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2294.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36881040", "exec_time": "529 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2294.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2295.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36874011", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2296.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36775796", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 37, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2296.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 67, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2296.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 16, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2296.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2297.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36742253", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2298.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36727087", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2298.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2299.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36685971", "exec_time": "264 ms", "memory": "8000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2299.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "23.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45453518", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "23.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "230.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44611639", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "230.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2300.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36653364", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2301.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36626349", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "16300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2301.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2302.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36622683", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2302.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2303.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36558623", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 54, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "2303.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2304.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36523976", "exec_time": "623 ms", "memory": "27200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2305.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 275, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36499551", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "7300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2305.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2306.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36456958", "exec_time": "623 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2307.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36436055", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "4800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2307.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2308.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36435906", "exec_time": "264 ms", "memory": "4800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2309.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36435880", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "4800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "231.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44606031", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "231.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2310.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36413490", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "2310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2311.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36376338", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "7400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2311.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2313.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36314395", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2313.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2314.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36278818", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "6700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2314.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2315.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36278390", "exec_time": "607 ms", "memory": "4600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2315.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2316.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 401, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36254101", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "5500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( T a , T b)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 90, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & x)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 175, "parameters": [], "filename": "2316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2317.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36236038", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "5900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2317.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2318.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36213172", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2318.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2319.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/368/submission/36151469", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "5900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 125, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 46, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "232.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44604826", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2320.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45435873", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2321.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45337670", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2321.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2322.cpp", "nloc": 108, "token_count": 1828, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45315060", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "10800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 43, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "writeln2", "long_name": "writeln2()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 5, "name": "readln", "long_name": "readln()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 55, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it , Head head , Tail ... tail)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["it", "head", "tail"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 51, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( const string & s , char c)", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 32, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 62, "name": "read_one", "long_name": "read_one()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 79, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( int k , int now)", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["k", "now"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 293, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 62, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( double a)", "start_line": 104, "end_line": 104, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( int a)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( const char * a)", "start_line": 106, "end_line": 106, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( string a)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( long long a)", "start_line": 108, "end_line": 108, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( long a)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( unsigned long a)", "start_line": 110, "end_line": 110, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( unsigned int a)", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( char a)", "start_line": 112, "end_line": 112, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( double a)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( int a)", "start_line": 114, "end_line": 114, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( const char * a)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( string a)", "start_line": 116, "end_line": 116, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( long a)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( long long a)", "start_line": 118, "end_line": 118, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( unsigned long a)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( unsigned int a)", "start_line": 120, "end_line": 120, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( char a)", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( vector<Type> & a)", "start_line": 122, "end_line": 122, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 99, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( vector<vector<Type>> & a)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( vector<Type> & a)", "start_line": 124, "end_line": 124, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 63, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( vector<vector<Type>> & a)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 125, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "print_no_space", "long_name": "print_no_space( pair<Type1,Type2> & a)", "start_line": 126, "end_line": 126, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( pair<Type1,Type2> & a)", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "writeln2", "long_name": "writeln2( Head head , Tail ... tail)", "start_line": 128, "end_line": 128, "parameters": ["head", "tail"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( Head head , Tail ... tail)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["head", "tail"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( double & a)", "start_line": 130, "end_line": 130, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( int & a)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( string & a)", "start_line": 132, "end_line": 132, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( long long & a)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( char & a)", "start_line": 134, "end_line": 134, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( pair<Type1,Type2> & a)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 68, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( vector<Type> & a)", "start_line": 136, "end_line": 136, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "readln", "long_name": "readln( Head & head , Tail & ... tail)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["head", "tail"], "filename": "2322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2323.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45306243", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 55, "name": "subseq", "long_name": "subseq( string a , string b)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2323.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2323.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2324.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 270, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45165776", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 252, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "2324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2325.cpp", "nloc": 79, "token_count": 778, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45148325", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 35, "name": "isvalid", "long_name": "isvalid( ll x , ll y , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["x", "y", "n", "m"], "filename": "2325.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 80, "name": "modexpo", "long_name": "modexpo( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2325.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 66, "token_count": 559, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 215, "parameters": [], "filename": "2325.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 153, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2326.cpp", "nloc": 87, "token_count": 486, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/45123985", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 25, "used_headers": 24, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 301, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 231, "parameters": [], "filename": "2326.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 119, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2327.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 289, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44844419", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 264, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2327.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2328.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44685621", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 285, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "2328.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2329.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 462, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44476820", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 54, "token_count": 455, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "2329.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "233.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44601653", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "233.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2330.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44472949", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "2330.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2331.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44351678", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 56, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "2331.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2332.cpp", "nloc": 93, "token_count": 720, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44278751", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 51, "name": "custom_hash::splitmix64", "long_name": "custom_hash::splitmix64( uint64_t x)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 39, "name": "custom_hash::operator ( )", "long_name": "custom_hash::operator ( )( uint64_t x) const", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 73, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( long long x , unsigned long long y , long long p)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 60, "token_count": 510, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 301, "parameters": [], "filename": "2332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 183, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2333.cpp", "nloc": 78, "token_count": 572, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44227526", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 16, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "maxx", "long_name": "maxx( LL & a , LL & b)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "minn", "long_name": "minn( LL & a , LL & b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "boostIO", "long_name": "boostIO()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "int_gcd", "long_name": "int_gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( LL a , LL b)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 65, "name": "poww", "long_name": "poww( LL base , LL exp , LL mod)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["base", "exp", "mod"], "filename": "2333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 319, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 205, "parameters": [], "filename": "2333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2334.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 288, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44188312", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2334.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 237, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2334.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2335.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 330, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/44168069", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "2335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2336.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 523, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43728531", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 6, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 483, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "2336.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2337.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 369, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43720183", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 14, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2337.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 268, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2337.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 23, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "2337.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2338.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 338, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43715395", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 35, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact( ll n)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2338.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 278, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2338.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2339.cpp", "nloc": 72, "token_count": 458, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43706185", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 128, "name": "build", "long_name": "build( int i)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "2339.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 185, "parameters": [], "filename": "2339.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "234.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44601028", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2340.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 284, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43701050", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 103, "name": "calc", "long_name": "calc( int idx , int cur)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["idx", "cur"], "filename": "2340.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 85, "name": "build", "long_name": "build( int idx , int cur)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["idx", "cur"], "filename": "2340.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "2340.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2341.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 347, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43667659", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 14, "name": "make", "long_name": "make( char c)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "2341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "make", "long_name": "make( char c1 , char c2)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["c1", "c2"], "filename": "2341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 38, "name": "make", "long_name": "make( char c1 , char c2 , char c3)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["c1", "c2", "c3"], "filename": "2341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 246, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "2341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2342.cpp", "nloc": 183, "token_count": 1125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43664514", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 32, "nloc": 137, "token_count": 812, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "2342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 137, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "modInv", "long_name": "modInv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 164, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "2342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 166, "end_line": 176, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "2342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "mpower", "long_name": "mpower( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 178, "end_line": 190, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 51, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 192, "end_line": 201, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2343.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 566, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43661982", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 42, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const pair<A,B> & p)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "2343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 67, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const vector<A> & v)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "2343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 51, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( const string & s , char c)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "2343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "2343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 61, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "2343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 109, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( int n , string s)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["n", "s"], "filename": "2343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 54, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 185, "parameters": [], "filename": "2343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2344.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43479169", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 124, "name": "rec", "long_name": "rec( int p , int r , bool used)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["p", "r", "used"], "filename": "2344.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2344.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2345.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 423, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43454204", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 346, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2345.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2346.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 282, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43437530", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "2346.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2347.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 421, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43430281", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 41, "name": "isdivisible", "long_name": "isdivisible( int num)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "2347.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 360, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "2347.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2348.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43428081", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 121, "name": "dp", "long_name": "dp( int x , int sum , int dig)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "sum", "dig"], "filename": "2348.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 36, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2348.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2349.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43427993", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 257, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2349.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "235.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 342, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44595719", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 310, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2350.cpp", "nloc": 84, "token_count": 435, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43427837", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 20, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 57, "name": "isDivByEight", "long_name": "isDivByEight( string s)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2350.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 203, "parameters": [], "filename": "2350.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2351.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 374, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43427686", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 274, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( string s)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2351.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2351.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2352.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 392, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43427635", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 21, "used_headers": 19, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 25, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 291, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 217, "parameters": [], "filename": "2352.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2353.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 374, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43423579", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 274, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( string s)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2354.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 423, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43423433", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 346, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2354.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2355.cpp", "nloc": 84, "token_count": 435, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43421970", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 20, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 57, "name": "isDivByEight", "long_name": "isDivByEight( string s)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2355.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 205, "parameters": [], "filename": "2355.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2356.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 418, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43419122", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 41, "name": "isdivisible", "long_name": "isdivisible( int num)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "2356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 357, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2357.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43418334", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 121, "name": "dp", "long_name": "dp( int x , int sum , int dig)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "sum", "dig"], "filename": "2357.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 36, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2357.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2358.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 392, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43418245", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 21, "used_headers": 19, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 25, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 291, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 217, "parameters": [], "filename": "2358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2359.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43418122", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 257, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2359.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "236.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44576457", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2360.cpp", "nloc": 70, "token_count": 551, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43262918", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 24, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 18, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2360.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 332, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "2360.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 59, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 171, "end_line": 187, "parameters": [], "filename": "2360.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2361.cpp", "nloc": 70, "token_count": 551, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43262843", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 24, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 18, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2361.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 332, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "2361.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 59, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 171, "end_line": 187, "parameters": [], "filename": "2361.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2362.cpp", "nloc": 137, "token_count": 679, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43217358", "exec_time": "436 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 31, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 27, "name": "MOD", "long_name": "MOD( int a , int b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "max3", "long_name": "max3( ll a , ll b , ll c)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "2362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 68, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 42, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 117, "name": "bfs", "long_name": "bfs( int s)", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 201, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 68, "token_count": 321, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 203, "end_line": 337, "parameters": [], "filename": "2362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 135, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2363.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43090608", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2363.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2364.cpp", "nloc": 87, "token_count": 754, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/43089438", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 52, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 74, "end_line": 74, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 65, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 76, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 78, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 92, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 94, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "modinv", "long_name": "modinv( ll a , ll p)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 110, "parameters": ["a", "p"], "filename": "2364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 357, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 114, "end_line": 174, "parameters": [], "filename": "2364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2365.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42793077", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 236, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2366.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/550/submission/42538432", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 289, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2366.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2367.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/45440446", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2367.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2368.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/45305099", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2368.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "237.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 361, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44572279", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 91, "name": "try_kuhn", "long_name": "try_kuhn( short v)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "237.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "237.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2370.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 446, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44983584", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 80, "name": "modexpo", "long_name": "modexpo( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "intpoint", "long_name": "intpoint( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "2370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "isvalid", "long_name": "isvalid( ll x , ll y , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x", "y", "n", "m"], "filename": "2370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "2370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2371.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44476090", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2371.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2372.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44447913", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "8100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "2372.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2373.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44438590", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 13, "name": "fun", "long_name": "fun( int x)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2373.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 145, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "2373.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 45, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "2373.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2374.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44415693", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2374.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2375.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 225, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44364576", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2375.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2375.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2375.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2376.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44337010", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2376.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2377.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44082530", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2377.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2378.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 130, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/44081769", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2378.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2379.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43714132", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2379.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "238.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44571849", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "238.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2380.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43691163", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 19, "name": "fast_io", "long_name": "fast_io()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2380.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2380.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2381.cpp", "nloc": 61, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43680414", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 30, "used_headers": 29, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "2381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2382.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43649833", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "11800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2382.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2383.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 216, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43647246", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2383.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2384.cpp", "nloc": 76, "token_count": 542, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43582397", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 229, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 50, "parameters": [], "filename": "2384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "modInv", "long_name": "modInv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "2384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "2384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "mpower", "long_name": "mpower( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 51, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 94, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2385.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 324, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43347433", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 14, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2385.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 56, "name": "num_to_string", "long_name": "num_to_string( int x)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2385.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 168, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "2385.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 16, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "2385.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2386.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43089926", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2386.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2387.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 531, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43082492", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 52, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 65, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 78, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 183, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 187, "end_line": 209, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "modinv", "long_name": "modinv( ll a , ll p)", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 219, "parameters": ["a", "p"], "filename": "2387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 225, "end_line": 239, "parameters": [], "filename": "2387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2388.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/43023678", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "2388.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2389.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42835488", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2389.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "239.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44560404", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2390.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 477, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42788798", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 27, "used_macros": 27, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 54, "name": "pow", "long_name": "pow( lnt a , lnt b , lnt p)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["a", "b", "p"], "filename": "2390.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( lnt a , lnt p)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["a", "p"], "filename": "2390.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "makedata", "long_name": "makedata()", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "2390.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "2390.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2391.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42536020", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2391.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2392.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42461270", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 25, "name": "home", "long_name": "home()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2392.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2392.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2393.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42244512", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 164, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2393.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 42, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "2393.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2394.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42221796", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2394.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2395.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42216425", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2395.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2396.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42196732", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2396.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2397.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42180589", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2397.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2398.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42170806", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2398.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2399.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/42087788", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 27, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( int x , int y)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2399.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 25, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( int x , int y)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2399.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 64, "parameters": [], "filename": "2399.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "24.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45451539", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "24.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "240.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44552777", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "240.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2400.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41977430", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 10, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2400.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2401.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41921738", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 14, "parameters": [], "filename": "2401.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2402.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41757785", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2402.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2403.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41754359", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2403.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2404.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41740247", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "6800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2405.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41534920", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 23, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "prn", "long_name": "prn( T first)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["first"], "filename": "2405.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 25, "name": "prn", "long_name": "prn( T first , Args ... args)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["first", "args"], "filename": "2405.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2405.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2406.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 346, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41534414", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "11800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 59, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2406.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2406.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2406.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "2406.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2407.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41506824", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2407.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2408.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41271240", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2408.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2409.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/41192155", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it)", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "2409.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 41, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "2409.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 64, "parameters": [], "filename": "2409.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "241.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44548410", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "241.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2410.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 300, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40989377", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 86, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( int & x)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2410.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "getc", "long_name": "getc()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2410.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "2410.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2411.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40935077", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2411.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2412.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40927820", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2412.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2413.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40874506", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2413.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2414.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40701253", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2414.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2415.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40689746", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2415.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2416.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40618073", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "2416.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2417.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40598760", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2417.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2418.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40598002", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2418.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2419.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40560911", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2419.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "242.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44547601", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 203, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "242.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2420.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40527880", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "2420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2421.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/363/submission/40479064", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2421.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2422.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45674665", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2422.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2423.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 307, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45636846", "exec_time": "390 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 15, "name": "stop", "long_name": "stop()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2423.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 231, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "2423.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2424.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45579057", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2424.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2425.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45467254", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2425.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2426.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45455701", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( int a , int b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2426.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "sub", "long_name": "sub( int a , int b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2426.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 42, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2426.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2426.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2427.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45448145", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 219, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 128, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "2427.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2428.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45414016", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2428.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2429.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 380, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45379464", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2429.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 65, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "n", "m"], "filename": "2429.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "2429.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "243.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44545859", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "243.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2430.cpp", "nloc": 152, "token_count": 505, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45377043", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 17, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "modint::modint", "long_name": "modint::modint()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 34, "name": "modint::modint", "long_name": "modint::modint( long long arg)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["arg"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 32, "name": "modint::operator +=", "long_name": "modint::operator +=( const modint & other)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["other"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "modint::operator *=", "long_name": "modint::operator *=( const modint & other)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["other"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 34, "name": "modint::operator -=", "long_name": "modint::operator -=( const modint & other)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["other"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 24, "name": "modint::operator +", "long_name": "modint::operator +( const modint & other) const", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["other"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 24, "name": "modint::operator -", "long_name": "modint::operator -( const modint & other) const", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["other"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 24, "name": "modint::operator *", "long_name": "modint::operator *( const modint & other) const", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["other"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 10, "name": "modint::operator int", "long_name": "modint::operator int() const", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 25, "name": "modint::operator ++", "long_name": "modint::operator ++()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 30, "name": "modint::operator --", "long_name": "modint::operator --()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 20, "name": "modint::operator ++", "long_name": "modint::operator ++( int)", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 175, "parameters": ["int"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 20, "name": "modint::operator --", "long_name": "modint::operator --( int)", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 187, "parameters": ["int"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 18, "name": "modint::operator ==", "long_name": "modint::operator ==( const modint & other) const", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 195, "parameters": ["other"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 18, "name": "modint::operator !=", "long_name": "modint::operator !=( const modint & other) const", "start_line": 199, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["other"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 64, "name": "modint::operator ^", "long_name": "modint::operator ^( T arg) const", "start_line": 209, "end_line": 235, "parameters": ["arg"], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 16, "name": "modint::inv", "long_name": "modint::inv() const", "start_line": 239, "end_line": 243, "parameters": [], "filename": "2430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2431.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 306, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45313630", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2431.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "lin", "long_name": "lin()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2431.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "2431.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2432.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45258483", "exec_time": "389 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 13, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll x)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2432.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2432.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2433.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 409, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45247279", "exec_time": "139 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 15, "macro_count": 23, "used_macros": 23, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 99, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 46, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( long long x)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 25, "name": "Rand", "long_name": "Rand( int l , int r)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "2433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "2433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2434.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45172034", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "MOD", "long_name": "MOD( ll & x)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 187, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 45, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "2434.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2435.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45166420", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "8100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 34, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2435.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2435.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2436.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 323, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45148688", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 26, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "2436.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 191, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 62, "parameters": [], "filename": "2436.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2437.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45130234", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2437.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2438.cpp", "nloc": 132, "token_count": 684, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45123718", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 10, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 42, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 60, "name": "inq", "long_name": "inq( ll k , ll q)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["k", "q"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 42, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 62, "name": "cubr", "long_name": "cubr( ll a)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 161, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 20, "name": "possible", "long_name": "possible( ll q)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["q"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 31, "name": "correct", "long_name": "correct( int x , int xx)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 189, "parameters": ["x", "xx"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 51, "name": "dsumm", "long_name": "dsumm( ll x , ll k)", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 211, "parameters": ["x", "k"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 94, "name": "dcount", "long_name": "dcount( ll x)", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 243, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "lg10", "long_name": "lg10( ll x)", "start_line": 245, "end_line": 255, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 305, "end_line": 355, "parameters": [], "filename": "2438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2439.cpp", "nloc": 78, "token_count": 751, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/45039249", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 14, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 41, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "EQ", "long_name": "EQ( double a , double b)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( T a , T b)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "toStr", "long_name": "toStr( T x)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 51, "name": "splitStr", "long_name": "splitStr( const string & s , vector<T> & out)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["s", "out"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "two", "long_name": "two( int n)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "isOnBit", "long_name": "isOnBit( int n , int b)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "onBit", "long_name": "onBit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "offBit", "long_name": "offBit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "lastBit", "long_name": "lastBit( int n)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "cntBit", "long_name": "cntBit( int n)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 161, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 68, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 187, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 253, "parameters": [], "filename": "2439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "244.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44539647", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2440.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 282, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44929506", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "2440.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2441.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 459, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44926899", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "35200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "fastpow", "long_name": "fastpow( ll n , ll x)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "2441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 56, "name": "fastpowDouble", "long_name": "fastpowDouble( double n , ll x)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "2441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "my_mod", "long_name": "my_mod( ll num , ll mod)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["num", "mod"], "filename": "2441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 75, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int cur = 1000000)", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 169, "parameters": ["1000000"], "filename": "2441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 171, "end_line": 215, "parameters": [], "filename": "2441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2442.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44821165", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2442.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2443.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 246, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44671363", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 239, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2443.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2444.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44541384", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2444.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2445.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44494316", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 68, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2445.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2445.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2446.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44444515", "exec_time": "389 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2446.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2447.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44420075", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "3500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 56, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 64, "name": "dp", "long_name": "dp( int rem)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["rem"], "filename": "2447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "2447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2448.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44412296", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "2448.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2449.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44378100", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2449.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "245.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44537273", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "245.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2450.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44328775", "exec_time": "170 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "2450.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2451.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44276958", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2451.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2452.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44272360", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2452.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2453.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44106879", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2453.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2454.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/44047705", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2454.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2455.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43949731", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 80, "name": "get", "long_name": "get( int size)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["size"], "filename": "2455.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2455.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2456.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43925956", "exec_time": "920 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2456.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2457.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43893035", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2457.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2458.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43816108", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2458.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2459.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43812739", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 217, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2459.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "246.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 279, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44530587", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 267, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "246.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2460.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43810112", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "2460.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2461.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43800646", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 223, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2461.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2462.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43742193", "exec_time": "623 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2462.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2463.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43740790", "exec_time": "623 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2463.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2464.cpp", "nloc": 81, "token_count": 689, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43705506", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 362, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "2464.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "modInv", "long_name": "modInv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 58, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "2464.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "2464.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "mpower", "long_name": "mpower( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2464.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 51, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 100, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2464.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2465.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43680589", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "15700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2465.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2466.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43627715", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 18, "parameters": [], "filename": "2466.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2467.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43627698", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2467.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2468.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 414, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43604058", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 391, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2468.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2469.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43603505", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 176, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2469.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 42, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "2469.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "247.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 279, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44523534", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 141, "parameters": [], "filename": "247.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2470.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43539460", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 52, "parameters": [], "filename": "2470.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2471.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43440741", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "2471.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2472.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 980, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43271629", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "15700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "get", "long_name": "get()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const pair<T1,T2> & cont)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["out", "cont"], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 65, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const vector<T> & cont)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["out", "cont"], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 48, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const set<T> & cont)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["out", "cont"], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 68, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const map<T,U> & cont)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["out", "cont"], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 87, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , vector<vector<T>> & cont)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["out", "cont"], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 88, "name": "setup_io", "long_name": "setup_io( string input_file = \"\" , string output_file = \"\")", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["\"\"", "\"\""], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "get_time", "long_name": "get_time()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 50, "name": "get_duration", "long_name": "get_duration( std :: chrono :: _V2 :: system_clock :: time_point start_time , std :: chrono :: _V2 :: system_clock :: time_point end_time)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["start_time", "end_time"], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "sign", "long_name": "sign( ld x)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 62, "name": "pow", "long_name": "pow( ll x , ll exp , ll mod)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "exp", "mod"], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "2472.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2473.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43158522", "exec_time": "655 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2473.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2474.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43155081", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "12800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 276, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2474.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2475.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 417, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43075486", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 60, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2475.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "ad", "long_name": "ad( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2475.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "sub", "long_name": "sub( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2475.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2475.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "divi", "long_name": "divi( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2475.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 109, "name": "pre", "long_name": "pre( ll k)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "2475.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "2475.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2476.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43034212", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2476.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2477.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/43023921", "exec_time": "561 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "2477.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2478.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42873873", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2478.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2479.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42866476", "exec_time": "467 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2479.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "248.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44520888", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "248.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 42, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2480.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42859683", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2480.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2481.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 248, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42832495", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 32, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 72, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2481.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2482.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42816193", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2482.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2483.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42738816", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2483.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2484.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 350, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42736615", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 24, "used_headers": 23, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 93, "name": "forn", "long_name": "forn( i , N)", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["i", "N"], "filename": "2484.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 46, "name": "forn", "long_name": "forn( _ , t)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 163, "parameters": ["_", "t"], "filename": "2484.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2485.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42659875", "exec_time": "467 ms", "memory": "15700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 45, "name": "get_sum", "long_name": "get_sum( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2485.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "2485.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2486.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42657939", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 26, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 54, "parameters": [], "filename": "2486.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2487.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 262, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42606864", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2487.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2488.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 226, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42594003", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 65, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( int i)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "2488.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2488.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2489.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42554026", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 77, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll i , ll x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["i", "x"], "filename": "2489.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2489.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "249.cpp", "nloc": 106, "token_count": 602, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44515052", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 30, "used_macros": 30, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 13, "name": "two", "long_name": "two( int n)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 20, "name": "test", "long_name": "test( int n , int b)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "set_bit", "long_name": "set_bit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "unset_bit", "long_name": "unset_bit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "last_bit", "long_name": "last_bit( int n)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 31, "name": "ones", "long_name": "ones( int n)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 163, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 67, "name": "modPow", "long_name": "modPow( ll a , ll b , ll MOD)", "start_line": 177, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "modInverse", "long_name": "modInverse( ll a , ll p)", "start_line": 207, "end_line": 213, "parameters": ["a", "p"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 41, "name": "isPrime", "long_name": "isPrime( ll x)", "start_line": 215, "end_line": 233, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 263, "end_line": 327, "parameters": [], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2490.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42553911", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 77, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll i , ll x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["i", "x"], "filename": "2490.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2490.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2491.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 307, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42534780", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 25, "used_headers": 24, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 240, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "2491.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2492.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42495374", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 63, "name": "genFib", "long_name": "genFib()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "2492.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 40, "name": "genCount", "long_name": "genCount()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2492.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2492.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2493.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 573, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42488191", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 93, "name": "getint", "long_name": "getint()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 69, "name": "mulD", "long_name": "mulD( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 88, "name": "exp", "long_name": "exp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 51, "name": "poww", "long_name": "poww( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "2493.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2494.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42453924", "exec_time": "311 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 229, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "2494.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2495.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 488, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/474/submission/42449456", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "tostr", "long_name": "tostr(string&s,auto num)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2495.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "toint", "long_name": "toint(auto&num,string s)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2495.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact(auto n)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2495.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod(auto a,auto b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2495.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm(auto a,auto b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2495.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 209, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "2495.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2496.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45696797", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2496.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2497.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45430510", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "UH_0X", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2497.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2498.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45392406", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 16, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2498.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2499.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 131, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45343861", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2499.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "25.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45448935", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "25.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "250.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 292, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44492949", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 279, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 56, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2500.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45244736", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2500.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2501.cpp", "nloc": 111, "token_count": 2412, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45170812", "exec_time": "186 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 38, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( t & a)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 43, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( pair<t,t1> & p)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 53, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( vector<t> & V)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["V"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 53, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( deque<t> & D)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["D"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( vector<t> & V , ll dim)", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["V", "dim"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( deque<t> & D , ll dim)", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["D", "dim"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( set<t> & S , ll dim)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["S", "dim"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( multiset<t> & M , ll dim)", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["M", "dim"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 52, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( priority_queue<t,vector<t>> & P , ll dim)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["P", "dim"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( priority_queue<t,vector<t>,greater<t>> & P , ll dim)", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["P", "dim"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( t a)", "start_line": 153, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( pair<t,t1> p)", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( vector<t> & V)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 157, "parameters": ["V"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 49, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( deque<t> & D)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["D"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( set<t> & S)", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 161, "parameters": ["S"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( multiset<t> & M)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 163, "parameters": ["M"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 91, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( priority_queue<t,vector<t>> & P)", "start_line": 165, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["P"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 96, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( priority_queue<t,vector<t>,greater<t>> & P)", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 167, "parameters": ["P"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( const Arg & arg , const Args & ... args)", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["arg", "args"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( Arg & arg , Args & ... args)", "start_line": 177, "end_line": 177, "parameters": ["arg", "args"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "GCD", "long_name": "GCD( t a , t b)", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 191, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "LCM", "long_name": "LCM( t a , t b)", "start_line": 193, "end_line": 193, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "abs", "long_name": "abs( t a , t b)", "start_line": 195, "end_line": 195, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "abs", "long_name": "abs( t a)", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 197, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int a , int b)", "start_line": 199, "end_line": 199, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( double a , double b)", "start_line": 201, "end_line": 201, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ld a , ld b)", "start_line": 203, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 205, "end_line": 205, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( int a , int b)", "start_line": 207, "end_line": 207, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( double a , double b)", "start_line": 209, "end_line": 209, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ld a , ld b)", "start_line": 211, "end_line": 211, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 213, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "StringToVector", "long_name": "StringToVector( string s)", "start_line": 215, "end_line": 215, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "StringToVectorInt", "long_name": "StringToVectorInt( string s)", "start_line": 217, "end_line": 217, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "NumberToString", "long_name": "NumberToString( t number)", "start_line": 219, "end_line": 219, "parameters": ["number"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "StringToNumber", "long_name": "StringToNumber( string s)", "start_line": 221, "end_line": 221, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "StringToNumberInt", "long_name": "StringToNumberInt( string s)", "start_line": 223, "end_line": 223, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 235, "end_line": 267, "parameters": [], "filename": "2501.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2502.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45152780", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2502.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2503.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 118, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45150989", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2503.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2504.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45075744", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 80, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "2504.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2504.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2505.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45072047", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 81, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2505.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2506.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 414, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45053506", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 80, "name": "modexpo", "long_name": "modexpo( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2506.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "intpoint", "long_name": "intpoint( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "2506.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "isvalid", "long_name": "isvalid( ll x , ll y , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x", "y", "n", "m"], "filename": "2506.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2506.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2507.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 80, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/45035543", "exec_time": "186 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 74, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "2507.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2508.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/44919695", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 25, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "fastpow", "long_name": "fastpow( ll n , ll x)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "2508.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 56, "name": "fastpowDouble", "long_name": "fastpowDouble( double n , ll x)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "2508.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "my_mod", "long_name": "my_mod( ll num , ll mod)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["num", "mod"], "filename": "2508.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2508.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 193, "parameters": [], "filename": "2508.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2509.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 91, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/44733543", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2509.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "251.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44484327", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 65, "name": "modpow", "long_name": "modpow( ll base , ll exp , ll modulus)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["base", "exp", "modulus"], "filename": "251.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "251.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2510.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/44232900", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2510.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2511.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 128, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/44184172", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2511.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2512.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 112, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/44104005", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 90, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "2512.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2513.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/44103950", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2513.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2514.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/44026842", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 108, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2514.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2514.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2515.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 308, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/44022116", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 94, "name": "Read", "long_name": "Read( Drake & x)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2515.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 47, "name": "write", "long_name": "write( Drake x)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2515.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( Drake x)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2515.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 32, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2515.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "2515.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2516.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 326, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43901060", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 91, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & x)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2516.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 29, "name": "writep", "long_name": "writep( T x)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2516.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 30, "name": "write", "long_name": "write( T x)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2516.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( T x)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2516.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 72, "parameters": [], "filename": "2516.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2517.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43718268", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 14, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2517.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 95, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "2517.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 16, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "2517.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2518.cpp", "nloc": 196, "token_count": 1115, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43718135", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Grey", "function_count": 15, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , pair<S,T> const & p)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 73, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , vector<T> const & v)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * name , T && arg1)", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 34, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 62, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * names , T && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 52, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( lli a , lli b)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 54, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( lli a , lli b)", "start_line": 56, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 72, "name": "getprimes", "long_name": "getprimes()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 108, "name": "primefactorise", "long_name": "primefactorise( int n)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 106, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 62, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( lli a , lli b)", "start_line": 108, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 71, "name": "getbinary", "long_name": "getbinary( lli x , lli size)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["x", "size"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 13, "name": "dist", "long_name": "dist( pll a , pll b)", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 46, "name": "makenode", "long_name": "makenode()", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 168, "parameters": [], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 86, "name": "insert", "long_name": "insert( tnode * root , string s)", "start_line": 170, "end_line": 183, "parameters": ["root", "s"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 77, "name": "search", "long_name": "search( tnode * root , string s)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 198, "parameters": ["root", "s"], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 203, "end_line": 233, "parameters": [], "filename": "2518.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2519.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43714185", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2519.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "252.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44483362", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2520.cpp", "nloc": 69, "token_count": 350, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43586417", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 31, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 27, "name": "MOD", "long_name": "MOD( int a , int b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2520.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "max3", "long_name": "max3( ll a , ll b , ll c)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "2520.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 68, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2520.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2520.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2520.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 42, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2520.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 201, "parameters": [], "filename": "2520.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2521.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 524, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43582476", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2521.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "modInv", "long_name": "modInv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 58, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "2521.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 60, "end_line": 70, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "2521.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "mpower", "long_name": "mpower( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 72, "end_line": 84, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "2521.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 51, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 86, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2521.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2522.cpp", "nloc": 127, "token_count": 777, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43490216", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 26, "used_headers": 26, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 41, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan( int64_t & a , int64_t & b = IX , int64_t & c = IX)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["a", "IX", "IX"], "filename": "2522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 74, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( int64_t a , int64_t b , int64_t c)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "2522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 77, "name": "find_prime", "long_name": "find_prime( int64_t n)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "inverse", "long_name": "inverse( int64_t a)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 157, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 42, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int64_t a , int64_t b)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( int64_t a , int64_t b)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 181, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 224, "name": "K_matcher", "long_name": "K_matcher( string p , string q)", "start_line": 183, "end_line": 255, "parameters": ["p", "q"], "filename": "2522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 263, "end_line": 297, "parameters": [], "filename": "2522.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2523.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43437286", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "2523.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2524.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43090655", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2524.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2525.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 493, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43082617", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 52, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2525.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2525.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 65, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2525.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 78, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 183, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2525.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 187, "end_line": 209, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2525.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "modinv", "long_name": "modinv( ll a , ll p)", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 219, "parameters": ["a", "p"], "filename": "2525.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 95, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 225, "end_line": 239, "parameters": [], "filename": "2525.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2526.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 97, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/43066548", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 85, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2526.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2527.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42798963", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2527.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2528.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42536061", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2528.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2529.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 114, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42464068", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2529.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "253.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44472239", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "253.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2530.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 114, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42463951", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2530.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2531.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42420086", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "2531.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2532.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42340697", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2532.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2533.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 115, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42339652", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 77, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2533.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2534.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42303401", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2534.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2535.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42251300", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 18, "parameters": [], "filename": "2535.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2536.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42204705", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2536.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2537.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42150886", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2537.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2538.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 124, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/42094316", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2538.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2539.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41990673", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2539.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "254.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44470608", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2540.cpp", "nloc": 195, "token_count": 2204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41907962", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "7900 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 40, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "pa3::pa3", "long_name": "pa3::pa3( int x = 0 , int y = 0 , int z = 0)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["0", "0", "0"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 48, "name": "pa3::operator <", "long_name": "pa3::operator <( const pa3 & p) const", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 48, "name": "pa3::operator >", "long_name": "pa3::operator >( const pa3 & p) const", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 30, "name": "pa3::operator ==", "long_name": "pa3::operator ==( const pa3 & p) const", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 33, "name": "pa3::operator !=", "long_name": "pa3::operator !=( const pa3 & p) const", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "pa4::pa4", "long_name": "pa4::pa4( int x = 0 , int y = 0 , int z = 0 , int w = 0)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["0", "0", "0", "0"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 63, "name": "pa4::operator <", "long_name": "pa4::operator <( const pa4 & p) const", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 63, "name": "pa4::operator >", "long_name": "pa4::operator >( const pa4 & p) const", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 36, "name": "pa4::operator ==", "long_name": "pa4::operator ==( const pa4 & p) const", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 151, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 39, "name": "pa4::operator !=", "long_name": "pa4::operator !=( const pa4 & p) const", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "pa2::pa2", "long_name": "pa2::pa2( int x = 0 , int y = 0)", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["0", "0"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "pa2::operator +", "long_name": "pa2::operator +( pa2 p)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 175, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "pa2::operator -", "long_name": "pa2::operator -( pa2 p)", "start_line": 177, "end_line": 177, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 30, "name": "pa2::operator <", "long_name": "pa2::operator <( const pa2 & p) const", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 183, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 30, "name": "pa2::operator >", "long_name": "pa2::operator >( const pa2 & p) const", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 189, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "pa2::operator ==", "long_name": "pa2::operator ==( const pa2 & p) const", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 195, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "pa2::operator !=", "long_name": "pa2::operator !=( const pa2 & p) const", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 201, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "Point::Point", "long_name": "Point::Point( double x = 0 , double y = 0)", "start_line": 223, "end_line": 223, "parameters": ["0", "0"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "Point::operator +", "long_name": "Point::operator +( Point p)", "start_line": 225, "end_line": 225, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "Point::operator -", "long_name": "Point::operator -( Point p)", "start_line": 227, "end_line": 227, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "Point::operator *", "long_name": "Point::operator *( double a)", "start_line": 229, "end_line": 229, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "Point::operator /", "long_name": "Point::operator /( double a)", "start_line": 231, "end_line": 231, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "Point::absv", "long_name": "Point::absv()", "start_line": 233, "end_line": 233, "parameters": [], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "Point::norm", "long_name": "Point::norm()", "start_line": 235, "end_line": 235, "parameters": [], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 30, "name": "Point::operator <", "long_name": "Point::operator <( const Point & p) const", "start_line": 237, "end_line": 241, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "Point::operator ==", "long_name": "Point::operator ==( const Point & p) const", "start_line": 243, "end_line": 247, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "dot", "long_name": "dot( Vector a , Vector b)", "start_line": 261, "end_line": 265, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "cross", "long_name": "cross( Vector a , Vector b)", "start_line": 267, "end_line": 271, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 33, "name": "parareru", "long_name": "parareru( Point a , Point b , Point c , Point d)", "start_line": 275, "end_line": 281, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 90, "name": "distance_ls_p", "long_name": "distance_ls_p( Point a , Point b , Point c)", "start_line": 283, "end_line": 291, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 298, "name": "is_intersected_ls", "long_name": "is_intersected_ls( Segment a , Segment b)", "start_line": 293, "end_line": 315, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 109, "name": "segment_dis", "long_name": "segment_dis( Segment a , Segment b)", "start_line": 319, "end_line": 333, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 87, "name": "intersection_ls", "long_name": "intersection_ls( Segment a , Segment b)", "start_line": 335, "end_line": 349, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 22, "name": "itos", "long_name": "itos( int i)", "start_line": 353, "end_line": 361, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 54, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int v , int b)", "start_line": 365, "end_line": 375, "parameters": ["v", "b"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 49, "name": "distans", "long_name": "distans( double x1 , double y1 , double x2 , double y2)", "start_line": 379, "end_line": 387, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 84, "name": "beki", "long_name": "beki( int wa , int rr , int warukazu)", "start_line": 397, "end_line": 409, "parameters": ["wa", "rr", "warukazu"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 45, "name": "comb", "long_name": "comb( int nn , int rr)", "start_line": 429, "end_line": 443, "parameters": ["nn", "rr"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 81, "name": "gya", "long_name": "gya( int ert)", "start_line": 447, "end_line": 461, "parameters": ["ert"], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 481, "end_line": 513, "parameters": [], "filename": "2540.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2541.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 422, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41816402", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "tostr", "long_name": "tostr(string&s,auto num)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2541.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "toint", "long_name": "toint(auto&num,string s)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2541.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact(auto n)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2541.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod(auto a,auto b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2541.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm(auto a,auto b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2541.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "2541.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2542.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41740492", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2542.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2543.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 124, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41728182", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "2543.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2544.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41645484", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2544.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2545.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41581760", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2545.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2546.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41534479", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 59, "name": "modexp", "long_name": "modexp( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "2546.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2546.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2546.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 77, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2546.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2547.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 117, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41506912", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "used_macros": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 110, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2547.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2548.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41278285", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2548.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2549.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41274692", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2549.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "255.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44470211", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2550.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/41220355", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2550.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2551.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40983975", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2551.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2552.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 112, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40935172", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2552.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2553.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 102, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40875219", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 89, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2553.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2554.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40699962", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2554.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2555.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40606221", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "NoCalibre", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2555.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2556.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 91, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40596922", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 67, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "2556.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2557.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40586649", "exec_time": "186 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 22, "used_macros": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "fast_io", "long_name": "fast_io()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2557.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 65, "name": "io", "long_name": "io( string taskname)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["taskname"], "filename": "2557.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "2557.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2558.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40559422", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "2558.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2559.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40527949", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2559.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "256.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44470018", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2560.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40479380", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2560.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2561.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 382, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40313458", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "read_char", "long_name": "read_char()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "Init", "long_name": "Init()", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 68, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "2561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 28, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "2561.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2562.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40175265", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "2562.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2563.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 105, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40161157", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 80, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2563.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2564.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 96, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40157604", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "2564.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2565.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 115, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/40030746", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2565.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2566.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39804057", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2566.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2567.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 114, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39793247", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2567.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2568.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39756317", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2568.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2569.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 107, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39736598", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 69, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2569.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "257.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44469752", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2570.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39540040", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 15, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2570.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "lin", "long_name": "lin()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2570.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "2570.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2571.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39507306", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2571.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2572.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 120, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39458509", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2572.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2573.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39404823", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2573.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2574.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 293, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39272874", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 51, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( const string & s , char c)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "2574.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "2574.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 61, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( vector<string> :: iterator it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "2574.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 80, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2574.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2575.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39249773", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2575.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2576.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39085001", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2576.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2577.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39074469", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2577.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2578.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39031843", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2578.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2579.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39022073", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2579.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "258.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44469622", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2580.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/39015849", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 27, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 110, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2580.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 24, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 70, "parameters": [], "filename": "2580.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2581.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38989251", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2581.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2582.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38988604", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "2582.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2583.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38951842", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2583.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2584.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 369, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38950534", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2584.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2584.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "smin", "long_name": "smin( T & a , T val)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "val"], "filename": "2584.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "smax", "long_name": "smax( T & a , T val)", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 40, "parameters": ["a", "val"], "filename": "2584.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 66, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "2584.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 70, "parameters": [], "filename": "2584.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2585.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38694980", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2585.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2586.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38694808", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2586.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2587.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 112, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38650584", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2587.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2588.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38600792", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "2588.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2589.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38588684", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2589.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "259.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44469445", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "259.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2590.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 333, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38536975", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2590.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 82, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "2590.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2591.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38261741", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "6700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 98, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "2591.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2592.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 131, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38085667", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2592.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2593.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38062805", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 22, "used_headers": 22, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "2593.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2594.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/38001372", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "11200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2594.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2595.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37999850", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 29, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 94, "parameters": [], "filename": "2595.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2596.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37926939", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2596.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2597.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37881997", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 12, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2597.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2598.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37880952", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "5300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2598.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2599.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37866028", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 10, "name": "stop", "long_name": "stop()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2599.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2599.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "26.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45445648", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "26.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "260.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44467024", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "260.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2600.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37583265", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2600.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2601.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37541542", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "4400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 81, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "2601.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2602.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37536827", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 23, "used_headers": 23, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2602.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2603.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37471157", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2603.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2604.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37372804", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2604.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2605.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 414, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37351126", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 26, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2605.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2605.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact( ll n)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2605.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 39, "name": "is_vowel", "long_name": "is_vowel( char c)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "2605.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "getDistance", "long_name": "getDistance( ld x1 , ld y1 , ld x2 , ld y2)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "2605.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 63, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll base , ll p)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["base", "p"], "filename": "2605.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "2605.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2606.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 360, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37344100", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 94, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & x)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2606.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( T x)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2606.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( T x)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2606.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "write", "long_name": "write( T x)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2606.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2606.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2607.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 128, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37287887", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 67, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "2607.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2608.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37225852", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2608.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2609.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/702/submission/37118854", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2609.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "261.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44465472", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 241, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "261.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2610.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 79, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/45594522", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 72, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2610.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2611.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/45304065", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2611.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2612.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 91, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/45238450", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2612.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2613.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/45153008", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 100, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( int a , int b)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2613.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "2613.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2614.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/44469253", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "daru_baaz", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "used_macros": 23, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 82, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2614.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2615.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 132, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/44180888", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 53, "name": "bp", "long_name": "bp( int a , int b)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2615.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 63, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2615.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2616.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/44107327", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2616.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2617.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/43786137", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2617.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2618.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 93, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/42822006", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 90, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 2, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "2618.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2619.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/42004052", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2619.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "262.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 415, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44462983", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 63, "name": "powermodm", "long_name": "powermodm( ll x , ll n , ll M)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 7, "parameters": ["x", "n", "M"], "filename": "262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 52, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll _a , ll _b)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["_a", "_b"], "filename": "262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2620.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/42003425", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 95, "name": "memo", "long_name": "memo( int a , int b)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2620.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 66, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "2620.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2621.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/41921105", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 124, "name": "go", "long_name": "go( int a , int b)", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2621.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 58, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 18, "parameters": [], "filename": "2621.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2622.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 109, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/41250035", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2622.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2623.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 117, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/41193092", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 70, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2623.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2624.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 87, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/39975991", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2624.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2625.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 103, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/39702074", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2625.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2626.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 105, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/38963520", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "3300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "2626.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2627.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 106, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/38943111", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "3600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2627.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2628.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 130, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/38642320", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2628.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2629.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 433, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/38600689", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 426, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "2629.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "263.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44457748", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 207, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "263.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2630.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/38397872", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 82, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2630.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "write", "long_name": "write( ll y)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["y"], "filename": "2630.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( const ll y)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["y"], "filename": "2630.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 68, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2630.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2631.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 272, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/651/submission/38334989", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "3400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 87, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & t)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["t"], "filename": "2631.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2631.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2632.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/45186388", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "getSum", "long_name": "getSum( int x)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2632.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 70, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2632.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 52, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2632.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2633.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 204, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/44543549", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "jiao", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 106, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( int pos , int mx , int sum)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["pos", "mx", "sum"], "filename": "2633.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2633.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2634.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/44475381", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 61, "name": "init", "long_name": "init()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2634.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 37, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2634.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2635.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/44251413", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 35, "name": "good", "long_name": "good( int a)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2635.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 72, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "2635.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2636.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/44185665", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 33, "name": "p", "long_name": "p( int x)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2636.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 82, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2636.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2637.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 86, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/43994458", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2637.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2638.cpp", "nloc": 211, "token_count": 1093, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/43363166", "exec_time": "639 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 16, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 12, "macro_count": 40, "used_macros": 40, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 63, "name": "inq", "long_name": "inq( ll k , ll q , ll mod)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["k", "q", "mod"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 42, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 62, "name": "cubr", "long_name": "cubr( ll a)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 157, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 169, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 171, "end_line": 177, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 20, "name": "possible", "long_name": "possible( ll q)", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 189, "parameters": ["q"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 31, "name": "correct", "long_name": "correct( int x , int xx)", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 205, "parameters": ["x", "xx"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 51, "name": "dsumm", "long_name": "dsumm( ll x , ll k)", "start_line": 207, "end_line": 227, "parameters": ["x", "k"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 94, "name": "dcount", "long_name": "dcount( ll x)", "start_line": 229, "end_line": 259, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 39, "name": "lg10", "long_name": "lg10( ll x)", "start_line": 261, "end_line": 275, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 33, "name": "g", "long_name": "g( ll x , ll mod)", "start_line": 277, "end_line": 287, "parameters": ["x", "mod"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "is_digit", "long_name": "is_digit( char c)", "start_line": 289, "end_line": 295, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 43, "name": "Matrix::Matrix", "long_name": "Matrix::Matrix( int a_ , int b_)", "start_line": 305, "end_line": 323, "parameters": ["a_", "b_"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 144, "name": "MatrixMultiplication", "long_name": "MatrixMultiplication( Matrix M , Matrix N)", "start_line": 329, "end_line": 369, "parameters": ["M", "N"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 135, "name": "inqMatrix", "long_name": "inqMatrix( Matrix A , ll q)", "start_line": 373, "end_line": 427, "parameters": ["A", "q"], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 88, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 473, "end_line": 519, "parameters": [], "filename": "2638.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2639.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/43342850", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 35, "name": "sod", "long_name": "sod( int x)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2639.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 59, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2639.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "264.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44456354", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2640.cpp", "nloc": 9, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42996410", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "gt", "long_name": "gt( int x)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 5, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2640.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 47, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 9, "parameters": [], "filename": "2640.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2641.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42793376", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "21900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 98, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "2641.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2642.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 331, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42735766", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "$$_LoSeRs_$$", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2642.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2642.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 103, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int x , int sum , int digits)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["x", "sum", "digits"], "filename": "2642.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 60, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "2642.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2643.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 105, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42679256", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 31, "name": "sum", "long_name": "sum( int x)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2643.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 61, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "2643.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2644.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42263632", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 16, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 33, "name": "digitsum", "long_name": "digitsum( int key)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["key"], "filename": "2644.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 90, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2644.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2645.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42218856", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2645.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2646.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42152149", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "starve", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2646.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2647.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 98, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42152070", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "starve", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 33, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int x)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2647.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 52, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2647.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2649.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/42110997", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 121, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( int p , int d , int n = 10 , LL now = 0)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["p", "d", "10", "0"], "filename": "2649.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "2649.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2650.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 1036, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41955118", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 21, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 143, "name": "formcomm", "long_name": "formcomm( const T & a)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 7, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 86, "name": "formout", "long_name": "formout( const T & a)", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 8, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "addout", "long_name": "addout( const T & a)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "addout", "long_name": "addout( const string & a)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( Ts && ... ts)", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 10, "parameters": ["ts"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 60, "name": "outs", "long_name": "outs( It a , It b , string mid = \" \" , string fin = \"\\n\")", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["a", "b", "\" \"", "\"\\n\""], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "outs", "long_name": "outs( const T & l , string mid = \" \" , string fin = \"\\n\")", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 12, "parameters": ["l", "\" \"", "\"\\n\""], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 86, "name": "formin", "long_name": "formin( const T & a)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "memneed", "long_name": "memneed( const T & a)", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 14, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "addin", "long_name": "addin( T & a , char * buf)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["a", "buf"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "addin", "long_name": "addin( string & a , char * & buf)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["a", "buf"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "postin", "long_name": "postin( T & a , char * buf)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 16, "parameters": ["a", "buf"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "postin", "long_name": "postin( string & a , char * & buf)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 16, "parameters": ["a", "buf"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 67, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( Ts && ... ts)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["ts"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "ins", "long_name": "ins( It a , It b)", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "ins", "long_name": "ins( T & l)", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["l"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "inl", "long_name": "inl( char * s)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "inl", "long_name": "inl( string & s)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 35, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( ll a)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 52, "name": "nxsl10", "long_name": "nxsl10( ll a)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 56, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2650.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2651.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41878559", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "36000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 70, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( int num , int left , int ct)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["num", "left", "ct"], "filename": "2651.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 60, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2651.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2652.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41758958", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2652.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "lin", "long_name": "lin()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2652.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 31, "name": "calc", "long_name": "calc( int x)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2652.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 63, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2652.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2653.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41568931", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 31, "name": "s", "long_name": "s( int x)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2653.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 50, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2653.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2654.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41505104", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 33, "name": "good", "long_name": "good( int x)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2654.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 64, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2654.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2655.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41319244", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 33, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int x)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2655.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 64, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2655.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2656.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 90, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41315386", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 33, "name": "isperfect", "long_name": "isperfect( int x)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2656.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 49, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2656.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2657.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41263974", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 35, "name": "isOk", "long_name": "isOk( int x)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2657.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 71, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2657.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2658.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/41153708", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 88, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2658.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2659.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 113, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/919/submission/40988861", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 33, "name": "testTen", "long_name": "testTen( int val)", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 12, "parameters": ["val"], "filename": "2659.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 49, "name": "permutate", "long_name": "permutate( int idx)", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["idx"], "filename": "2659.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "2659.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "266.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44456017", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2660.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 268, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/45188468", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 244, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2660.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2661.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/44984537", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "modpow", "long_name": "modpow( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2661.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 255, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2661.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2662.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/44755167", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2662.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2663.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 319, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/44699041", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 19, "name": "init_ios", "long_name": "init_ios()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "2663.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 38, "name": "poz", "long_name": "poz( string & s)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2663.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "2663.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2664.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 258, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/44335679", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 235, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2664.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2665.cpp", "nloc": 61, "token_count": 388, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/44296524", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Zero", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 49, "name": "fac", "long_name": "fac()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2665.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 30, "name": "C", "long_name": "C( lint a , lint b)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2665.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 294, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 175, "parameters": [], "filename": "2665.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2666.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 339, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/43771548", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 19, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 27, "used_macros": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 113, "name": "rec", "long_name": "rec( int i , int y)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 82, "parameters": ["i", "y"], "filename": "2666.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 69, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 84, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "2666.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2667.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 268, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/43180260", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 58, "name": "newton", "long_name": "newton( int n , int k)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "2667.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2667.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2668.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/42814192", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 46, "name": "C", "long_name": "C( int n , int k)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "2668.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2668.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2669.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 361, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/42205091", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 333, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2669.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "267.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44454852", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2670.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/41827617", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 49, "name": "get", "long_name": "get( string s)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "2670.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2670.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2671.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 370, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/41755145", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 16, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2671.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "lin", "long_name": "lin()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2671.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 242, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "2671.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2672.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 319, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/41560537", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 61, "token_count": 312, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 173, "parameters": [], "filename": "2672.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 165, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2673.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 316, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/41445446", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 19, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "2673.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2674.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/41285358", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 121, "name": "go", "long_name": "go( int p)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "2674.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 75, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "2674.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2675.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/41224862", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 125, "name": "final_right", "long_name": "final_right( int fp , string s2 , int pos , int i)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["fp", "s2", "pos", "i"], "filename": "2675.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2675.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2676.cpp", "nloc": 317, "token_count": 2526, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/41004460", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 49, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "seti::seti", "long_name": "seti::seti()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 17, "parameters": [], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 44, "name": "seti::seti", "long_name": "seti::seti( initializer_list<T> o)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 18, "name": "seti::operator [ ]", "long_name": "seti::operator [ ]( int i)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "vectori::vectori", "long_name": "vectori::vectori( size_t n , T e = T())", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["n", "T"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "vectori::vectori", "long_name": "vectori::vectori( InputIt first , InputIt last)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["first", "last"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "vectori::vectori", "long_name": "vectori::vectori( initializer_list<T> o)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "vectori::operator +=", "long_name": "vectori::operator +=( T o)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "vectori::operator +=", "long_name": "vectori::operator +=( initializer_list<T> o)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "vectori::operator +=", "long_name": "vectori::operator +=( vectori<T> o)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "chash::operator ( )", "long_name": "chash::operator ( )( int x) const", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const vector<T> & arr)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 125, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const vectori<T> & arr)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 157, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 76, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const map<T,P> & arr)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 191, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const set<T,P> & arr)", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 225, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const seti<T> & arr)", "start_line": 231, "end_line": 259, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "__debugg", "long_name": "__debugg( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 267, "end_line": 271, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 76, "name": "__debugg", "long_name": "__debugg( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 275, "end_line": 291, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "Pair::Pair", "long_name": "Pair::Pair( const X1 & x , const Y1 & y)", "start_line": 311, "end_line": 311, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 5, "name": "Pair::Pair", "long_name": "Pair::Pair()", "start_line": 313, "end_line": 313, "parameters": [], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "Pair::Pair", "long_name": "Pair::Pair( const X1 & x)", "start_line": 317, "end_line": 317, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "Pair::operator +", "long_name": "Pair::operator +( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 321, "end_line": 325, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "Pair::operator -", "long_name": "Pair::operator -( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 329, "end_line": 333, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "Pair::operator *", "long_name": "Pair::operator *( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 337, "end_line": 341, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "Pair::operator /", "long_name": "Pair::operator /( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 345, "end_line": 349, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "Pair::operator +=", "long_name": "Pair::operator +=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 353, "end_line": 359, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "Pair::operator -=", "long_name": "Pair::operator -=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 363, "end_line": 369, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "Pair::operator *=", "long_name": "Pair::operator *=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 373, "end_line": 379, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "Pair::operator /=", "long_name": "Pair::operator /=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 383, "end_line": 389, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "Pair::operator <", "long_name": "Pair::operator <( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 393, "end_line": 403, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "Pair::operator <=", "long_name": "Pair::operator <=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 407, "end_line": 417, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "Pair::operator >", "long_name": "Pair::operator >( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 421, "end_line": 431, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "Pair::operator >=", "long_name": "Pair::operator >=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 435, "end_line": 445, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "Pair::operator ==", "long_name": "Pair::operator ==( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 449, "end_line": 453, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "Pair::operator !=", "long_name": "Pair::operator !=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 457, "end_line": 461, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "Pair::swap", "long_name": "Pair::swap( Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 465, "end_line": 471, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "makep", "long_name": "makep( const X & x , const Y & y)", "start_line": 479, "end_line": 483, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 44, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const Pair<X,Y> & p)", "start_line": 489, "end_line": 495, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 34, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & in , Pair<X,Y> & p)", "start_line": 501, "end_line": 507, "parameters": ["in", "p"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 35, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & in , vector<T> & arr)", "start_line": 537, "end_line": 549, "parameters": ["in", "arr"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 47, "name": "printi", "long_name": "printi( const T & arr , char skyr = '\\n')", "start_line": 555, "end_line": 575, "parameters": ["arr", "'\\n'"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 47, "name": "printi", "long_name": "printi( const T & arr , const string & skyr)", "start_line": 581, "end_line": 601, "parameters": ["arr", "skyr"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "printp", "long_name": "printp( const Pair<X,Y> & p , char skyr = ' ')", "start_line": 607, "end_line": 611, "parameters": ["p", "' '"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "printp", "long_name": "printp( const Pair<X,Y> & p , const string & skyr)", "start_line": 619, "end_line": 623, "parameters": ["p", "skyr"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "mini", "long_name": "mini( X & a , const Y & b)", "start_line": 633, "end_line": 643, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "maxi", "long_name": "maxi( X & a , const Y & b)", "start_line": 651, "end_line": 661, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "between", "long_name": "between( ll v)", "start_line": 671, "end_line": 675, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 28, "name": "between", "long_name": "between( ll X , ll v , ll Y)", "start_line": 681, "end_line": 685, "parameters": ["X", "v", "Y"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 35, "name": "fakt", "long_name": "fakt( ll a)", "start_line": 691, "end_line": 707, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 735, "end_line": 807, "parameters": [], "filename": "2676.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2677.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/40755862", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 50, "name": "C", "long_name": "C( int i , int n)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 14, "parameters": ["i", "n"], "filename": "2677.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2677.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2678.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/40583955", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 33, "name": "F", "long_name": "F( ll n)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2678.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "C", "long_name": "C( ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "2678.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "2678.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2679.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 246, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/40310719", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 56, "name": "dfs_1", "long_name": "dfs_1( int x , int loc)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x", "loc"], "filename": "2679.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 98, "name": "dfs_2", "long_name": "dfs_2( int x , int loc)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["x", "loc"], "filename": "2679.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 59, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "2679.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "268.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44452629", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2680.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 450, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/40172690", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 53, "name": "desperate_optimization", "long_name": "desperate_optimization( int precision)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["precision"], "filename": "2680.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 74, "name": "combin", "long_name": "combin( int n , int r)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["n", "r"], "filename": "2680.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 36, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast( double a , int b)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2680.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 61, "name": "calc", "long_name": "calc( int diff , int ada)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["diff", "ada"], "filename": "2680.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 175, "parameters": [], "filename": "2680.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2681.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 456, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/40166430", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 66, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["a", "n", "m"], "filename": "2681.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 105, "name": "calculateFact", "long_name": "calculateFact()", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "2681.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 62, "name": "nck", "long_name": "nck( int n , int k)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "2681.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2681.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2682.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/40079675", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 49, "name": "C", "long_name": "C( int n , int m)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["n", "m"], "filename": "2682.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "2682.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2683.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/476/submission/39891184", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 118, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( int i , int p , LD prob)", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 20, "parameters": ["i", "p", "prob"], "filename": "2683.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 80, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "2683.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2684.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 216, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45306393", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2684.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2685.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45034799", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 14, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2685.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "lin", "long_name": "lin()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2685.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "2685.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2686.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/44381631", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "2686.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2687.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/44253750", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2687.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2688.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 544, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/44153134", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 34, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & in , pair<T,R> & p)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["in", "p"], "filename": "2688.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 33, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & in , vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["in", "v"], "filename": "2688.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 35, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "2688.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 407, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2688.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2689.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 428, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/43786631", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 390, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2689.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "269.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44446259", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "269.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2690.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 481, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/42999104", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 439, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "2690.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2691.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 384, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/42818374", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 337, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2691.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2692.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/42350707", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "2692.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2693.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45687066", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "7300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 215, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( int pos , int prev)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["pos", "prev"], "filename": "2693.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "2693.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2694.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45687043", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "8600 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 215, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( int pos , int prev)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 28, "parameters": ["pos", "prev"], "filename": "2694.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "2694.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2695.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45672551", "exec_time": "343 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2695.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2696.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45637892", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 194, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2696.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2696.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2697.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45636721", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 296, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2697.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2698.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45589681", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "15800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 37, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 215, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 169, "parameters": [], "filename": "2698.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2699.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 410, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45581207", "exec_time": "405 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 328, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2699.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "27.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 338, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/45439295", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 329, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "27.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "270.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44445653", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2700.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45578995", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "5500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 125, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int x)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2700.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2700.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2701.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45576879", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "2701.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2702.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45568490", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2702.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2703.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45495231", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2703.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2704.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45484969", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2704.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2705.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45453826", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "2705.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2706.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45436212", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2706.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2707.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45426206", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "2707.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2708.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 216, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45306393", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 179, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2708.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2709.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/45034799", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 14, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2709.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "lin", "long_name": "lin()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2709.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "2709.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "271.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44442151", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2710.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/44381631", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "2710.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2711.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/44253750", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "2711.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2712.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 544, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/44153134", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 34, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & in , pair<T,R> & p)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["in", "p"], "filename": "2712.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 33, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & in , vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["in", "v"], "filename": "2712.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 35, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "2712.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 407, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "2712.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2713.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 428, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/43786631", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 390, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2713.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2714.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 481, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/42999104", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 439, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "2714.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2715.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 384, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/42818374", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 337, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2715.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2716.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/42350707", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "2716.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2717.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 462, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/41985828", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "2200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 10, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 426, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "2717.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2718.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/41570469", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "2718.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2719.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 448, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/41183757", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 19, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int x , int y)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "2719.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int x , int y , int z)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["x", "y", "z"], "filename": "2719.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 377, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "2719.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "272.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44433566", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "272.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2720.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 348, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/41136748", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 331, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "2720.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2721.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 430, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/41069909", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 30, "name": "getMax", "long_name": "getMax( int a , int b , int c)", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 6, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "2721.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 396, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2721.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2722.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/40892235", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2722.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2723.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/545/submission/40478856", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "2723.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2724.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/45695501", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2724.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2725.cpp", "nloc": 81, "token_count": 1887, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/45506521", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 36, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 15, "macro_count": 78, "used_macros": 77, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "zero", "long_name": "zero( T val , T & x)", "start_line": 253, "end_line": 253, "parameters": ["val", "x"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "zero", "long_name": "zero( T val , T & x , Targs & ... Fargs)", "start_line": 255, "end_line": 255, "parameters": ["val", "x", "Fargs"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( std :: istream & is , pair<T,T2> & p)", "start_line": 261, "end_line": 261, "parameters": ["is", "p"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 39, "name": "readN", "long_name": "readN( T & x , int n , int st = 0)", "start_line": 263, "end_line": 263, "parameters": ["x", "n", "0"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "readS", "long_name": "readS( set<T> & x , int n)", "start_line": 265, "end_line": 265, "parameters": ["x", "n"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & x)", "start_line": 267, "end_line": 267, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 25, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & x , Targs & ... Fargs)", "start_line": 269, "end_line": 269, "parameters": ["x", "Fargs"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , pair<T,T2> p)", "start_line": 289, "end_line": 289, "parameters": ["os", "p"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 54, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , vector<T> v)", "start_line": 291, "end_line": 291, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 54, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , set<T> v)", "start_line": 293, "end_line": 293, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 54, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , multiset<T> v)", "start_line": 295, "end_line": 295, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 71, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , map<T,T2> v)", "start_line": 297, "end_line": 297, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 48, "name": "outV", "long_name": "outV( T x , char del = ' ')", "start_line": 299, "end_line": 299, "parameters": ["x", "' '"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 70, "name": "outN", "long_name": "outN( T x , int n = - 1 , int st = 0)", "start_line": 301, "end_line": 301, "parameters": ["x", "1", "0"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 52, "name": "outAN", "long_name": "outAN( T x , int n = - 1 , int st = 0)", "start_line": 303, "end_line": 303, "parameters": ["x", "1", "0"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 50, "name": "outA2", "long_name": "outA2( T x , int n , int m)", "start_line": 305, "end_line": 305, "parameters": ["x", "n", "m"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( T x)", "start_line": 307, "end_line": 307, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( T x , Targs ... Fargs)", "start_line": 309, "end_line": 309, "parameters": ["x", "Fargs"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "srt", "long_name": "srt( T & a , int st , int fn , bool isArr)", "start_line": 313, "end_line": 313, "parameters": ["a", "st", "fn", "isArr"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "srt", "long_name": "srt( T & a , int st = 0 , int fn = 0)", "start_line": 315, "end_line": 315, "parameters": ["a", "0", "0"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "rev_num", "long_name": "rev_num( T a)", "start_line": 319, "end_line": 319, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "rev", "long_name": "rev( T & a , int st , int fn , bool isArr)", "start_line": 321, "end_line": 321, "parameters": ["a", "st", "fn", "isArr"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "rev", "long_name": "rev( T & a , int st = 0 , int fn = 0)", "start_line": 323, "end_line": 323, "parameters": ["a", "0", "0"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "sqr", "long_name": "sqr( ll a)", "start_line": 327, "end_line": 327, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "sqr", "long_name": "sqr( int a)", "start_line": 329, "end_line": 329, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "sqr", "long_name": "sqr( ld a)", "start_line": 331, "end_line": 331, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 71, "name": "phi", "long_name": "phi( int n)", "start_line": 335, "end_line": 335, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 75, "name": "bpm", "long_name": "bpm( ll a , ll n = - 2 , ll m = mod)", "start_line": 337, "end_line": 337, "parameters": ["a", "2", "mod"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ull a , ull b)", "start_line": 339, "end_line": 339, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 84, "name": "ero", "long_name": "ero( int n)", "start_line": 343, "end_line": 343, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 75, "name": "gcd_cb", "long_name": "gcd_cb( ll a , ll b , ll & x , ll & y)", "start_line": 347, "end_line": 347, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "fact_prec", "long_name": "fact_prec( int n = 20)", "start_line": 351, "end_line": 351, "parameters": ["20"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 45, "name": "fact_precd", "long_name": "fact_precd( int n = 146)", "start_line": 353, "end_line": 353, "parameters": ["146"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 37, "name": "str", "long_name": "str( ll a)", "start_line": 355, "end_line": 355, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 61, "name": "solution", "long_name": "solution()", "start_line": 365, "end_line": 393, "parameters": [], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 12, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 397, "end_line": 409, "parameters": [], "filename": "2725.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2726.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 85, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/45314461", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 78, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2726.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2727.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 112, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/45286979", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "2727.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2728.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 118, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/45282277", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "2728.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2729.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/45238177", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "WeDontCook", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2729.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "273.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44428053", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 50, "name": "findArea", "long_name": "findArea( float a , float b , float c)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "273.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "273.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2730.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 102, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/45236699", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 95, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2730.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2731.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 83, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44476575", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 80, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "2731.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2732.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44470855", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "2732.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2733.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 89, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44459103", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "coder", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 82, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "2733.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2734.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 85, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44336732", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 74, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "2734.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2735.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44290424", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "47000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2735.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2736.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 334, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44289044", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Grey", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 31, "used_macros": 31, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , pair<S,T> const & p)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "2736.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 73, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , vector<T> const & v)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "2736.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * name , T && arg1)", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "2736.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 62, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * names , T && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 50, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "2736.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "2736.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2737.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 89, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44056682", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "2737.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2738.cpp", "nloc": 10, "token_count": 79, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44042959", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "rua", "long_name": "rua( int k)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 7, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "2738.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 48, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "2738.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2739.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 166, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43798990", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2739.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "274.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 367, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44427759", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "194000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 285, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2740.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 83, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43552116", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 71, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2740.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2741.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42860399", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 16, "macro_count": 17, "used_macros": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "2741.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2742.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 84, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42801768", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 78, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2742.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2743.cpp", "nloc": 9, "token_count": 77, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42758334", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 70, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 17, "parameters": [], "filename": "2743.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2744.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 94, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42677678", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 77, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "2744.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2745.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42209318", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "brotechies", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2745.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2746.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 102, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41947407", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 52, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "2746.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2747.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 102, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41649692", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2747.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2748.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 99, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41637193", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "used_macros": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "2748.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2749.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41589933", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 83, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 15, "parameters": [], "filename": "2749.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "2749.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "275.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44422035", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "275.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2750.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 410, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41469560", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 63, "name": "itosm", "long_name": "itosm( ll x)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2750.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 67, "name": "stoim", "long_name": "stoim( string str)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["str"], "filename": "2750.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 59, "name": "binpow", "long_name": "binpow( ll x , ll st)", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["x", "st"], "filename": "2750.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 69, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 169, "parameters": [], "filename": "2750.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 36, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 225, "parameters": [], "filename": "2750.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2751.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 93, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41315368", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "2751.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2752.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41274656", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "2752.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 56, "name": "run", "long_name": "run()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2752.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 12, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "2752.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2753.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 77, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41258171", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 70, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2753.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2754.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41120663", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 52, "name": "dis", "long_name": "dis( int x1 , int y1 , int x2 , int y2)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "2754.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 78, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "2754.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2755.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 89, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41084637", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 82, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2755.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2756.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41067657", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 75, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "2756.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2757.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 101, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40939246", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 77, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "2757.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2758.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 121, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40915050", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 82, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "2758.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2759.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40842491", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "2759.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "276.cpp", "nloc": 79, "token_count": 631, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44421183", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "2100 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 34, "name": "init", "long_name": "init( int _n1 , int _n2)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["_n1", "_n2"], "filename": "276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 35, "name": "addEdge", "long_name": "addEdge( int u , int v)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["u", "v"], "filename": "276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 156, "name": "bfs", "long_name": "bfs()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 104, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( int u1)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["u1"], "filename": "276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 101, "name": "maxMatching", "long_name": "maxMatching()", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 171, "parameters": [], "filename": "276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 199, "parameters": [], "filename": "276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2760.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 107, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40819925", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "2760.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2761.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40727774", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "HuNau", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "2761.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2762.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/45555695", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "2762.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2763.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/45392488", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 16, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "2763.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2764.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/45305790", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "used_macros": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2764.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2765.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 267, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/45037196", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 15, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2765.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "lin", "long_name": "lin()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "2765.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "2765.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2766.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 304, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/44770854", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 10, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 67, "name": "removeZeros", "long_name": "removeZeros( string T)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["T"], "filename": "2766.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "2766.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2767.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 216, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/44453325", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "used_macros": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 22, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "2767.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2768.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/44249942", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2768.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2769.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/43269571", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "2769.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "277.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/489/submission/44419688", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "277.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2770.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/43080045", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "2770.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2771.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 304, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/42361059", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 291, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "2771.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2772.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/41601438", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 17, "macro_count": 9, "used_macros": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "2772.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2773.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/41257626", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 39, "name": "contin", "long_name": "contin( char str [ ])", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["]"], "filename": "2773.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2773.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2774.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 261, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/40479978", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "used_macros": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 31, "name": "is_quasi", "long_name": "is_quasi( int x)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 11, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "2774.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "2774.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2775.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/538/submission/40369906", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "used_macros": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "2775.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]}]
